Forgotten tune I dance among the sacred first is my temple hall the endless
Learness my home the ancient branches softly sway the forest opens one last
Gateway then slowly takes the road away taking a little bit what's up guys hi
you want to say hi to Lola Lola yeah they're saying my cat taped me last night
There you go. Yeah, that was actually pretty epic epic opening
So I hope you enjoyed that
It is 1137 a.m. In Los Angeles. Oh
Lola
business Lola
I am I programmed the nightbot like fucking great. It's crazy. It'll do really cool things now
if you go
exclamation point commands you can go and see all the commands and
Play around with them. Yeah
Exactly him again with cat strangler. Aren't they aren't they unhappy and strangled?
I'm not I'm not even gonna time you up for that because you wait you wait
I think he waited the whole song so you do deserve a little a little chance but hold on I'll show you how to
Look at the nightbot commands and there you go. I think it's like that or might be just
There you go. You can see all the commands there. There's like
20 at least
But Lola's very happy.
Are you happy?
Hi babe.
Yeah, the cats are very happy.
Hi, you're looking at me?
You're looking at me?
She's looking at me with beautiful eyes.
So how's everyone doing today?
I'm still in my pajamas.
There we go.
My PGs.
I was trying to put a background on, but.
Yeah, we do have, you know, for the guests.
I'll put the link up.
Hey, what's up, Elias?
How are you?
Good to see ya.
Good to see you. Hold on. Here we go. I'm on this channel. It hasn't been a while
You know, you were right. Elias. I think you do know my friend
Lucas because I was like, I was like, there's no way that's the same guy has named Lucas
But I don't know about some of the other stuff you said, but he's he's he's actually a nice guy
He's he's eccentric too. So how do you know I'm in stuff? That's interesting. Hi Lola. Hi, baby
I would never I would you know
They could eat it like the other night. Oh my god. Where have I been? I was on another channel
I was streaming on one called nightmare frequencies TV. It's just like enough starting to build another channel. Also, you know, I'm just gonna
You know beyond but I'll be on here and on that one probably for a little bit
But uh, you know, I've been around
Pretty you know, I've been streaming here for a couple days now
But any did I put the link up? Yeah, there you go. So if anyone wants to link or take it
We can see we had some really good I guess on last night. We had Karen. We had a Gotti
We had Mason the drummer's been back. Hey everybody
You know, I don't know if you all saw like, you know
Last night they played it when Bita came over to the channel and like, you know, she was so drunk and was saying really terrible things.
But when they played it on Samman's channel, you know how usually he just plays the clip from the channel?
He had someone do all this AI on it, like of me, all dirty and crazy screaming tricks.
And then they had her looking like a Kardashian, all nice and cool.
And then you could barely hear me.
But yeah, my neighbor did throw my doorbell
through my window that night because her high-pitched voice
disturbed the piece.
It was only 9.30 at night.
But yeah, my neighbor started kicking my middle door
and then through the doorbell, through the window, broke it.
So not very good and not very good, but um, yeah, I don't know
Um, I did end up showing like, you know, Bita's real picture and like Sam Man's real picture on my show
But they just edited that part out. I mean so it was really a little bit misleading
But I don't know. There's a lot of followers in that chat room
There's some cool people, but
Again, I'm not going to harass anybody if we're going anywhere, but they have been harassing
people going to mine.
So it's like if you happen to get harassed or called names, it's like, you know, that
might happen, but they don't know what they're talking about.
I mean, so, but I've been really good, hopefully someone will come up and we can have a chat.
Oh, yeah, you're just stretching out.
There she is.
Oh, she's stretched.
She's very comfortable.
Yeah, but they were saying,
because like, you know,
I put some catnip on my table and stuff
and my cat tucks his back.
Like he might be inside right now.
You know, he might have gone back outside,
but he was high on catnip
and I kind of reached over and grabbed the bag
and he like, you know, just kind of swatted me.
But, and then the people were like, oh, his cat,
even his cats hate him.
My cats do not hate me.
They don't, you love me.
No, I think she does love me. She's very comfortable. They're very, uh, they're very happy cats. My cats are awesome
I don't understand why people want to say shit about them and me like I'm like
you know, like, you know, I was very sad when Trix left,
but it's like, you know, I am understanding
that cats tend to wander.
I do let them out.
I mean, there are dangers too, but, you know,
I've had Lola for several years and she's been okay.
And like, Lenore's here.
You got Rudy, oh man, Rudy's at the table over there.
And so, yeah, but she's very, very comfortable
and all the cats are good.
That are here, but you know when we're not tricks left tucks came like the pretty much like the next few days, so
Pretty crazy
But yeah, I guess I have a lurker to ban too. You see lurk. I think it is. Let me see what happens. Hey, Jamie. What's up, Jamie?
I re-bamped the night night, but so it's really looking good
I might you want to look at the commands again because there's some new ones and
Yeah, that's miss Lola. Oh, aren't you aren't you comfortable?
there you go aren't you comfortable there's even an and there's a here's one like calling
people out of the shadows like you can also like unlock you see there you go yeah i but there's a
it's like i made it so um there's like a lot of random yeah there's a lot of random commands too
yeah you'll love it oh shut up shut up arthur you're such a faggot get out of here you're banned
leave salmon out of my mouth i'm pleased but leave my name just listen let your band you're not
I wish I think I had a banished command. Let me see. I don't know if I do, but let me see
Banished because Arthur's banished now
Did you like it? It's pretty cool, huh?
You see a man's name out of her mouth
How about he leaves my name out of his mouth and stop playing my content and or editing it to be something different, right?
Yeah, so if you don't respect the rules, you're just gonna be banned. Okay. We have J dog coming up. Let's welcome J dog
Yo
Psyche, what's up, bro? How you doing?
Good. How are you today here? I'll show you the story.
Just chilling, chilling, man.
Good. I don't know. Yeah, do you like the new, I have a big background.
I have, like, a little bit of a chat, you know, kind of like, you know, back to normal and, uh...
You happen to see Sandman last night? Like, what do you play for him?
Um, I saw little clips here and there, but I didn't see the whole thing. What had happened?
I heard I had something to do with you. Did he play your clip?
Yeah, he did, but then they edited it, so it's like, it was like, they made me all
scurvy and like screaming like trick, and then they had like, you know, like they
edited her to look like so good, and like...
They raised the microphone, turned down mine, and they edited it out when I showed their real faces, so it was just kind of ridiculous, you know.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Um, but, uh, you know, I wouldn't, I don't, I wouldn't want to stricke at him, but I did, like, I did, like, I worked with him, and they're not editing my stuff so much.
Yeah, Lola's very comfortable. Hi, Nancy. What do you think Nancy Nancy? They edited the hell out of that
Didn't they like it was like and then they made me look so bad
And there are people are like, oh, I got cooked. I don't think I got cooked
I mean, it's like but maybe if you saw you can barely I mean, maybe if you saw the
That clip you might think I did because they edited it
So it's like she looks so good and I look so terrible and then they started saying oh my cats hate me and and
I'm filthy and all this stuff. I mean, it's like a
You know, I didn't really have anybody there defending me, but you know, it's crazy.
Oh, yeah, there we go.
But I have a lot of you.
There we go.
You're going to love the new commands.
And there's some gamification to them, too.
I think some people can get points and stuff like that.
It's really cool.
I think you're like, like what I do with it.
There you go.
Everyone type cult, cult, cult, right?
Feel the static on your fingertips.
Yeah.
So there's Miss Lola.
Hi.
All right, she's a very, she's very comfortable.
See, my cats don't hate me, but it's like,
but Tux is like kind of a little bit feral.
And so-
Hold on a second.
My bad.
Yeah, and then my, you know, I have a cat and it will be to a saying, oh, you know, you like, you know, basically I killed tricks or something like that, or I let him let him run away, I should be out looking for him right now, like I'm supposed to be out like a month later.
Well, you already put the word out, right? You're getting to ready post something like online, like, hey, be a look out for this cat.
Right. So I don't understand, like, but then it's like, I don't know. It's like, I really like my cats do.
There's only so much you can do especially for a missing animal. I mean you get everything you can
I mean you can every day, too
I checked the uh, I check it and I look and there's sometimes there's cats that look like him and stuff
But I do have another cat that came back like uh tux and he wouldn't have come back and tricks
I had it left and so because they were fighting over territory right because they're both male cats
Yeah, okay, so they were trying to push each other out of the way to try to be a male
Yeah
And Tuxa, but yeah, there was like, I put Katnip on the table and then like someone was like, oh, look at his filthy table.
And then I like reached over and Tuxa like slapped my hand or whatever because he was, they get high on Katnip and they get a little bit aggressive.
Right. And then they're like, oh, look, even his cats hate him. Oh, his cats are so unlucky.
You know, oh, like they're so like abused and stuff like that.
You know, it's just so so so so ridiculous.
I don't even know most of these people, but there was a few people in the chat last night.
I saw that we're like calling her beta out and she got very defensive about.
But she's bringing up my mom and things like that,
bringing up my family.
She even brought up my dad.
Oh yeah, yeah, that's bad, bro.
Don't be bringing a family involved
with a couple like that.
Dude, she's one to say about, like,
her and Sandman are ones to say about,
oh, don't talk about the dead.
Don't talk about family members.
Don't be kids or this or that.
And what do they do?
They bring up the same children.
and he's like well you know he's like people bring up his mom and stuff but I never did and so why
so it's like but he's so he's like I don't care or so you know because people do it to me well
yeah just because he doesn't care it doesn't mean that you don't care though I mean it might be okay
for him but it might not be okay for other people
It was really hurtful. I mean, I need to fix that command because yeah, if you do the discord,
I need to fix that command guys because I did it wrong. I need to do a space in there so
the discord works right. But yeah, I did nightbot. I put like 50 commands in nightbot or whatever
and there's some game commands. I don't know. It's like there's really, there's some random ones.
It's really cool actually. I think you guys will have fun with the play. And there's still
There's a lot more new ones.
Okay, there, I updated the discord.
So try that again, discord, I fixed it.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, and I was like,
but I was like, you know, Meeta's mom passed away.
I wouldn't bring her up in a negative way.
Meeta was saying, my mom lives like cattlemen and stuff.
And it's like-
I heard that.
She was saying all that in the other night, right?
And she said it again.
Well, she was saying last night. She was just defending herself saying well
He said some he posted my my my my ex-fiance's picture. So yes, I just
Well, you didn't really post it was Katie who's the one who docks that picture and everybody else just shared it like I shared it online
I know you everybody else shared it. I didn't think Sam and sure
She shares it herself on on Instagram
you know she um she shares him so it's like she's she's like well it doesn't matter other
sites it just matters on youtube i i don't know you can't really like keep it all separate though
like that i mean it's like if you're gonna post it somewhere like why are you mad if it's like
other people say i don't know it's like a very double standard but uh yeah yeah she i mean it's
Yeah, they're the king and queen of them.
Oh my bad, I didn't mean to interrupt, like, in my back.
Not at all, but yeah, they're like, you know, they think they're prom king, prom queen or whatever, they think it's high school, they think it's middle school even.
I don't even know what, it's just very immature and stuff like that, right?
Yeah.
It's crazy.
But anyway, they did, it's very double standard, and they did, like, you know...
edit the fuck out of the clip they took out the part where I show their faces and stuff like that
they made this AI of me like so dirty and like you know looking crazy and stuff and then and
also she was saying that I like I robbed the store I steal like I like because I get copyright
you did not rob from the store the lady didn't charge you correctly it wasn't even your fault
I played the clip and it's different if you ran out of a store with the items like if you said
Oh, I'm gonna go get some stuff and then just walk out and not pay for it
And then they just they caught you like that. That's not what happened the little you see the clip you saw the clip
Yeah, yeah, yeah the clip of the lady. Yeah, she told you one price
And then you were leaving and then you know halfway down the street
The other lady comes starts screaming like a like a fucking crazy person. Oh William fire arms here
Oh, William, but no, dude that dude they're talking about something from like three years ago when I first came into like
Sandman's community and when I first like cross paths with beta like there was a story
Where I used to be a CEO and
Smuggled in cell phones into the prison. You didn't do it in your butt. Did you and
No, no, no, no, no, it wasn't even me. I was just part of the operation. I didn't even smuggle them in
It was the janitor who smuggled them in through the cleaning supplies. Okay. That's who was smuggling them in
What nobody smuggled in any phones in there, but yeah, so what you're on clumsy's recent
You know clumsy's like been attacking me a lot lately. I don't know if you're friends, you know what I saw about that
I was on clumsy. I didn't know you guys were you know, I know you guys had
Some kind of be I didn't know how bad and then I heard him calling like the F a g word and like
Like like I saw little clips of him like going at you heart. I'm like, what the fuck is what's going on like what happened there?
Like he right. Um, well, I mean it's
He um, he's mad about you know, so just me having where we're one in my chat
Like he used to be blazing me all the time like saying oh sake. Yeah, I'm gonna donate to you as soon as I can you're such a cool guy
I love being on your show. Thanks for having me on blah blah blah, and then he started saying I'm not
you know predator protector and now he's like saying oh fuck you psyche you know you're a you're
faggot and uh and you know um you know you you have and then he started like saying those attacks
like eat it that's like oh you know you have a you have the bkg on your chest and um you know you
are your cats where's tricks where's tricks i mean it's like it's just like the same kind of
shit right it's like so stupid uh poppy each other those attacks don't affect me because
know it's just trolling and I know like my cats love me and stuff so yeah yeah it's all it's all
you know it's all bullshit it's not real yeah oh we had Karen on last night Karen did call Bita
because Bill Bita was saying terrible things about her and so she was I think she called Bita on the phone
Yeah, she called her house and then Beat is like, if you call again, I'm gonna like, you know, sue you or whatever.
I don't know, it was ridiculous.
And but Karen was on last night and we had a great like probably half hour to an hour conversation.
And I see you guys the other time on on Alex's on the wiki IRL news time.
I see you guys on that one like couple days ago and stuff like that.
Yeah, beatacalls are also, it looks like, yeah, so, but and then Crystal Anne, I like, you know,
Ghostman over to Crystal Anne's show and like Q is like actually like puppeteering her now because
he tells her like who to have on like she didn't she didn't want to have Ghost on and then he tells
her to have Ghost on and then he put, she put Ghost up and then also who else?
um um it came over like somebody else came oh Karen came over there and then he was like oh have
her on like you know it's like but i'm banned from there but i do think that people should have
everybody like on their panel if they want you know it's like it's good sometimes it is
but uh Karen's a nice lady i don't know why you know she she gets hate they've been very mean to
her and she's a very generous like kind person she's not she's not like bad or anything like that
You know it's been through a lot and it's like she deserves a little bit. She's also like, you know knows a lot about the communities and stuff
So yeah, she's really like yeah, I gotta head out. I gotta head out man
I'll hit you up later if you're live later. I'll jump back on. Okay, man. It's good. Have a great day
You too, bro. I'll see you later. Peace out. Yeah
Yeah, do you guys like the, uh, do you guys like the nightbot commands?
It says the elders demand tribute, offer snacks, lost sleep, or fragments of dignity, the cult
piece on chaos and crumbs.
Very good. Yeah, there's some gamification ones when we get to the game
There's also like a lot of like a random
Responses and there's like certainly I don't know there's also like I guess I can like declare a winner
They can maybe I'll give away a codex membership to somebody random in the chat
Okay, so but you have to be okay
You guys they're commenting the chat and so you can be eligible because then once you do you can you're a little
Eligible to win I'll do like a free a free
membership for a month, okay
Anybody who wants to do that to the codex just make sure you comment right now before I announce the winner because it will be decided randomly
through the by nightbot through whoever is commenting in the chat
And and then you all you have to do send me your email address or something and I can plug you in there by tomorrow
Yep, you want to win it? Yeah
So, let's see, let's see, yeah, I think tomorrow I'll be able to program it in, but so let's
see.
Hey, I'm going to give you 30 seconds, I'll give it to Nancy, I'll probably give it to
Nancy.
Hey, there's Nick.
Okay, Nick's eligible.
Nancy, Jamie, okay.
So, yeah, it'll be, I'll give you a free month membership, and.
I have everything working there now it's actually really looking really good as I also put people's pictures if I could like most people
I put the channel if I could but there's like 800 people and so if you have a channel and you want you want to
Make sure it's connected
I can connect it to the probe your profile because most people that are in the chat are in the codex because
everybody that's
that's actually
They'll comment it on the show or so their name on the show are pretty much in there. So yeah, okay, so let's see
Okay, so I guess we have no one else. Okay comment now prove or hold your piece
I'll give you a little more minute to comment before I announce the winner
Okay, yeah, let's see who wins. Okay
I guess I go winner. I'll just I'll say I said a minute. So I'll just give you a minute and
Yeah, it's really cool though. You can actually like with the membership you can
I'll put your channel on the front page and stuff and that goes for anybody that becomes a member
There's a couple of membership tiers. I might yeah, I don't know, but it's it. I mean, it's really a really cool thing
I think you guys will love it. You should check it out. Anyway cold codex.me. Okay, you know that 30 seconds
Okay, I'm drinking my coffee right now
Yes, it is a refill, but yes, I went this morning and I bought
bought I bought one and so I'm entitled to refills until like 1 30 in the
afternoon when they closed so I think you can get another one today so anyway
okay let's I guess it's been 30 seconds and so I'm gonna put winner and whoever
gets this just you can go backstage and type your email address or contact me
on discord okay and with your email address and so I'm gonna do it five
Five, four, three, two, one, zero.
Let's see if this works.
Uh-oh, I did it wrong, huh?
There you go.
Let's see if this works.
Okay.
Oh, it says cult of psyche always wins.
Oh, look it, there you go, there you go, Liz.
Colts, oh, there we go, and the winner is,
it's me, I won, oh my God.
Hold on, I need to do it again.
I can't win, I already have a membership.
Let's see. I did not even subscribe to my channel. Oh my god. I don't know if I'm allowed to subscribe to my own channel and the winner is
Reality Nancy there you go. There you go reality Nancy you won the member of a month membership to there you go
Hey, what's up as rap big big gum? What's up?
Hopefully you're doing good. There you go Nancy. You know you won congratulations
Yeah, I'll put that in tomorrow. I can and you know, I'll make sure you get that actually can put it in tomorrow
So congratulations
Congratulations
Yeah, hey, what's up Osama Turk? She's
Kate's crying. I know I saw yesterday. Kate had posted that
She's like, oh, he's banivating everyone do your thing guys. I wasn't banivating. I had my channels weren't I have it
No, I've had no channels taken down or anything
So I'm allowed to have another channel, right?
And so that's why my that's why I didn't get in trouble for that
But she was trying to get me in trouble for that, you know, and the first night I started streaming she posted and stuff
Yeah
Oh, thank you very much raslin and dazzling nice to see oh my gosh. There's some new faces and new people in here
I appreciate you guys
Yeah, and I'll give away some more memberships
You know free memberships and stuff because I want a lot of people to check out but there is a free
There's a free membership too, and it's basically you also gets a couple of you Oracle
You know the Oracle is trained on the show and so she knows like everything about it. So yeah
So I will yeah, so I'm gonna I'm gonna leave it alone. Yeah, don't yeah
It's I don't know anything about her, you know her family
I don't want to talk about people's family because it's like I don't want people to talk about my family
And so it's like, you know, it's like I just I just and I I should just just tell the chat
Just like don't talk about the people's they're not on the show if they're or they're not on on YouTube
It's like just don't bring them up. But hey, hey, what's up guys? Hey Osama. Hey everybody. Yeah
Um, he heaves unhiding. Who's the person who's the unhiding? I don't know someone gets hidden
I don't I don't see some of the comments and so
But
Yeah, yeah, just don't talk about the kids because we're just you can delete those comments Jamie
Just delete the comments and you know, I just cuz a DUI times. Oh my gosh because you know
It's like you because then it will just be it's like not a popular thing to do either
And then it's like it just looks bad on me and she'll be like oh look
He's allowing this and stuff and it just it's just causes problems
And so I appreciate if you just like you know leave it to your own show or to
Talk about whatever you want, but well
Just don't do that if you if they do it again, then it's like, you know, they're not I just ask like respect respect Jamie
Jamie's you're you are I'm managing mods. So, okay. Yeah
So, uh, yeah
Just let like Jamie's like the top mod here. So just let her let her do her thing, please. So hey, what's up DUI times?
Yeah, so you saw the four song I played at the beginning. I have this little like this is kind of cool
This is like a little like
I got this on Etsy. It's like a little forest fairy in a jar kind of thing. It's kind of cool.
I have some cool stuff I got on Etsy a few years ago, but this is also collectible and it's like a little label on it.
Anam, and it says, Edinburgh, Scotland, Dr. Worthington,
number 27, these were limited edition.
I got number 27, there you go, that's a lucky number.
Hey, 55 people in the chat, wow, awesome.
Thank you for bringing people here.
I think somebody brought people here.
Appreciate you for like bringing people here.
Shout out to everybody.
So that's a really cool, yeah, that's really good.
Thank you, appreciate for bringing people here.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, so I went to Good Times the other night and Good Times was like kind of nice.
Yeah, I appreciate that, Brandon. I appreciate that. And I didn't see anybody breaking the rules,
but yeah, it's like if they could just stop bringing up people's family, that'd be cool.
And then it's like they can stay. Okay. Yeah. Who keeps, yeah, someone's promoting me. So I
appreciate that. Thank you so much.
Oh, she posted the live.
Okay, well, no one's being mean to me.
I didn't notice anybody being mean, but, you know,
so that's pretty good.
Well, thank you Kate for the for the publicity appreciate that how nice how nice of you and I thought you didn't like me anymore
So I think for the publicity shout out to everybody. Yeah, we've got great people here corruption is real
What's up corruption? You're in the codex, but I after yeah, I saw corruption in there
and
Everybody's pretty much in the codex if you've been part of the show. There's like 800 people or something like that
I did start putting people's avatars and it has been a while. So good to see you. Good to see everybody 58 people. Wow
That is awesome. Yeah, I was on another champ my other channel and it's like it was like people were like, oh my gosh
There's nobody there. I was brand new and stuff and you know, I was just taking a little breather
But it's great to see everybody here
How are we doing? Yeah, I haven't had McDonald's today, but you know, I might I mean it's like
You know they took the coffee off them off the
Up the value points menu because I could get coffee for a dollar there usually but now it's like, you know
$4 and all I can the only thing they have left on it is like a fries the $2 fries
Also, if like I guess it's like the Dodgers win or something like that or the angels or something you get free
Like free fries with a big Mac or something like that
You know, I'm kind of like getting burnt out on McDonald's a little bit
Yeah
Yeah, it sucks. I mean if they had it's for like a I've probably been eating McDonald's a lot for like the past six months
I you miss the sausage a McMuffin for two dollars. Yeah, I mean, it's like they they saw like on the menu now
They have like hardly anything on it
They had like four items and stuff like that on it and I'll see what they have on it. I'll show you
because the app
I really recommend using the app, because that's like, you know, you can save a lot of money with the app, like, you know, at least like I was saving like probably five, 10 bucks, but it still is kind of expensive, you know, for some of the stuff.
I remember when McDonald's used to be like $1.99, they had happy meals for $1.99 and stuff, and now it's like, you know.
They're like five bucks or something so you know the prices of all going up and stuff the food is better though
Cuz I used to not be able to eat it very often. I get sick if I eat it too much
But let's see what's I'll show you guys what's on the menu there right now for the value
If you have the app if you have the app
I
Don't know it's going very slow
Yeah, there you go. Okay, so the app says we go rewards you go deals
And so there's like, it's a free chicken McNuggets
with a minimum purchase of $15, a free breakfast sandwich.
So you have to pay 15 bucks
and you get a free egg and cream muffin, I guess, right?
McDouble Burger's gotten smaller, like a slider, oh no.
Oh, the free medium fries, cause the angels won.
$2 fries any time or also and also if you use a little kiosk you can get up multiple times you get oh, yeah
When they had dollar cheeseburgers. Yeah, they had the cheeseburgers used they used to have the dollar menu
They may change it to the make value menu and stuff like that working spurlock. I know like look at this
I mean, it's like I've eaten it every day. I didn't get fat
there's actually some guy that has had like a big mac every day and he's like really weird
he's like a bull haircut and stuff and he's but he goes and gets one every day and he's like a normal
size too um and one dollar hash brown i like the hash browns but it shouldn't say hash browns because
they give you one hash brown for the dollar um it's not hash browns you know they should say
Yeah, I just I've been working on it a lot. It's actually I'm looking so good. It's it's crazy.
Yeah, I can show you a little bit. I can I can look I actually the Oracle is working. So I'll
ask the Oracle about Nick today. Let me see if I can bring it up real quick. If you go to codex.me
you can check out what it says about you. But I'll look at Nick right now. And if anyone else wants
me to read their entry, I'll do it today. Okay, so you go over here and you go to Oracle right there.
You can see there's the oracle right there.
And then you can go, if I go Nick Johnson.
Okay, oops, I spelled it wrong.
It spelled it like the German way, N-I-C-H, like, okay.
Nick Johnson, I mean it's a,
we'll say he's searching the archive.
Okay, it's searching. There we go. It's okay. It says the archive holds Nick Johnson as a named recurring warm
Network figure whose presence has calcified from casual visitor into something more structurally significant
He is the man with the hat that reads his own name a self labeling that doubles as authentication
It gives the imposter current running through the streams lore the psychonomicon notes that he and psyche share a birthday
You know what we do
Maybe that's I don't know if that's right both Capricorn. Are you Capricorn? I'm not sure
We were born both in Los Angeles perimeters. That's not right either both citing
Endurances are defining quality a pairing the archive does not treat as coincidence
He exercises on camera shirtless and sweaty rolls tires jumps trampolines
And has been mythologized as seeing rituals in the static flow at 333 a threshold name embedded in the channel's own anthem
The real Nick is always the one wearing the hat
Well, I don't know about that, but your friend got out of jail today.
Yeah, kids. Yeah. Yeah.
Jamie's Jamie's kind of enforcing that rule.
I can't see that. I can't see either, because I do.
I do have like a lot of people blog.
So I have never seen that. I haven't seen any of that comment.
So maybe I have the person blocked. Maybe they're just an asshole, you know.
Hey, cryptic blue. Good to see you. Good to see you.
Your friend got a jail. That's awesome. Congratulations.
Now I don't I don't see anybody saying that stuff. So I must have them blocked
I do have a lot of people blocked usually if just people are talking shit about me and other chats
I blocked them and then I don't even see them, but it's like, you know, most of them are just Tony
I'm sure like, you know, there's Lady Bathory. Let's see who else I'm I can look up. Let me see who else can I look up today?
Anybody in the chat I can look up
Reality Nancy again. Let me see. Here's reality Nancy. So let's see what it says about reality Nancy if I go Oracle
Yeah, I hooked up with the Oracle with like some credits and so so if they go reality Nancy
Did she just won a membership today?
Okay, reality Nancy and here we go. It's searching. Okay. Let's see what it says. It says
Reality Nancy exists in the archive as infrastructure made briefly visible her name
Surfaces an episode 500 thanks to passing during the psyche awakens after party her labor the quiet
Scaffolding behind the mini man's interview rather than any performance of her own the psychonomicon codes her archetype as the departing legacy
I think it
the one who migrates between platform communities without permanent tribal claim.
Well, that's good, you know, because you're receiving the post-public validation as a
mechanism of graceful exit rather than the deeper entrenchment.
Her intercession on another's behalf, or Psyche's intercession on hers,
has seated what the archive now tracks as the advocated absent, a pattern where Psyche acts
as a diplomatic bridge for those blocked or excluded from other spaces.
She is not a character who sought the center, she's a character who made the center possible,
then stepped away.
The most essential figures rarely appear in the light.
Well, Nancy's been here since the beginning of the show.
She's awesome.
Let's see.
OK, so there you go.
Coped cryptic blue.
Good to see you.
So there we go.
And then I can look at, yeah.
So anyway, there's really cool stuff.
Let's see what else I have.
There are a couple.
See if it goes network map.
Here's everybody on the map.
Like, look, there's like a.
There's all the connections, 284 recurring figures.
So these are all the people that have been on multiple times.
And look, now I have all most of the avatars.
There's Joe Shipley right there.
Joe Shipley, by the way.
You know there really has been unfair like someone can't there's DJ electric someone came on and like was like
Oh, Joe is perverted because he was like, you know watch the Blair witch
With like a kid or something like that now is like a family friend
I mean, it's like but there are like, you know trip and sip was like, whoa, I wonder if he did it
I mean, I mean, it's like so
People are just like so in the gutter, but yeah, you can actually go like this and make it bigger like there you go
See and then I will show all the there's me. There's me. I guess it will show all there's bronze bird. Oh my god
He's kind of see clothes. Oh my god. There's Kate. Oh my god. Thanks, uh,
Alexander McQueen there's ghost and
You know, so there's Sam and he's connected to be to see it's perfect and then she's connected to
Alex McQueen and there's the J dog and then
J dogs connected the beta and I mean this but connected okay, but I also have some other ones too
this is called the return and
There's no connections yet there, but I think then we have this one to the current and there we go
there's Lisa Jordana, you know, there's a
Miser oh my god remember Miser tiger butterfly 27 appearances. She hasn't been on the show for quite a while. There's same man, okay?
page
Alexander mares
DJ Electra
Chona
Joker I need to pick some of the avatars, but there's there's crystal more. I don't think that's the real picture of crystal Marie, but
There's Mason the drummer, you know, so I have like there
Anybody that I they're traveling gypsy. I couldn't find her real channel anymore
I think she must have left YouTube, but yeah, she turned on me. Oh, there's Rudy. He doesn't have a channel. I'm a Leviathan there. Oh my god
Someone yeah, there's J dog. Is that Arthur? Oh my god, and then
yeah but there's some cool charts right there um let's see what else there is there's a leader board
okay there i am on the leader board okay there's a timeline of the show um oh yeah there's some
there's some trading cards too let's see um there's also a tarot reading let's do a tarot reading
for the chat so here's the tarot deck okay
So pull a reading. I'll do a three-card reading. I'll pull it right there. Okay, there we go
So these are some of these are the cards that I created for the the website. So we have the seven of glitches, okay?
It says seven processes
Processes a new trust six the trader is patient and in no hurry strategy
This quiet works right up until it doesn't decide whether the cleverness is worth the solitude.
Okay, so that's the quiet breach. Okay, then this is two of glitches.
It's a stalemate loop. So you might be right now experiencing some kind of stalemate.
So it's two presences blindfolded, each waiting for the other to crash first.
The deadlock is a decision disguised as patience.
One of you.
has to open your eyes. Okay, so maybe there's a situation with another person, but we also have
the siren, okay, and it says the commanding glass. The siren governs the tide of feeling in any room
and never once gets wet. Mastery of emotion is at this level can move people or drown them without
the siren.
um, feeling a thing. Yeah, because the sirens actually in ancient Greek mythology were these, uh,
they were kind of birds. Hey, yeah. How many times have you been on the site? Yeah, I can look at that.
Let me see. Hold on. I'm going back up. Um, or so it says, if I go, if I, yeah, I can show you what it
looks like when I just search for a person. Here we go. Um, it'll say all the appearance, it'll say
most of the appearances. Okay. So it says, if I go, if I search for you right there, you can go Nick
And there you are. Okay. Oh, that's not your picture. I need to I need to get your channel next so I can put your real picture in there
I have some other Nick Johnson says person mentioned passing conversation. Nick Johnson is this entertainer guest known for providing visual comedy and
Antics during live streams with a model like appearance
He brings levity and physical humor to the show's panel discussion and casual broadcasts
He appears frequently alongside psyche in the core guest roster contributing to the show's entertaining atmosphere
He's been a consistent presence across multiple stream formats, appearing most frequently
during the lengthy open panel tarot and chat sessions that characterize the show's Sunday
and Monday night programming.
He has participated in casual lifestyle streams, including workout sessions and post-coffee
hangouts, helping psyche celebrate milestones like YouTube partner status.
His appearance can span from chaotic all night panels to more intimate casual streams, suggesting
he's a reliable entertainer for various show formats.
He appears regularly as side core guests, including Janet,
Bita, Tiger Butterfly, and Alexander.
He, primary relationship is with host Psyche,
with whom he appears frequently.
He maintains consistent presence in the revolving guest
lineup through specific dynamics or storylines
between him and other guests are not clearly
documented and available to date.
Okay, so there's like, look at all the episodes.
Here's like 42 appearances that has cataloged.
So all these episodes, you can go
and you can see all the mixed appearances right here.
um let me see if there's like a short I can show you um let me see um yeah but um
and yeah we had we had a zitty a diddy part we had a zitty party we call it um let's see yeah
and so yeah these are all those appearance and then I had some quotes probably and here's his
quote says if you if you're talking about a threesome with two women that I am more open to
but even that still I don't know about that but I would say I'm more open to that more open well
So you're kind of open to, like, with the...
He's more open.
I guess he said no to the three-some with me.
Yeah, 42, like Jackie Robinson.
You like that number? Okay, good.
Yeah, I might have asked Nick to do a three-some.
I don't know who the third person would be, but, you know...
I'm still looking for, like, another...
Yeah, Chris Kay, I guess.
Chris K is pretty funny. I guess he got evicted, but yeah, Chris K used to say yeah
He was really interested in doing a chatter bait with me and or something like that
but I guess he just got evicted from his place and
You know, I don't want to moving in here because I don't think my family wants to not see moving in with me, but
You know or neo-nazi. There are some funny appearances with them though. Yeah, what happened to Chris?
Yeah, he got evicted from his townhouse in Vegas, I guess and so I don't know where he is, but yeah
Also, it was sad. He had a cat. It was really cool like a little orange cat that passed away and stuff
That was pretty sad, but yeah, I haven't seen him for like I haven't seen him probably for a month or two, but
Who picked who I kicked out Chris K? I
What do you get kicked out for I?
I guess bothering the people but I'll show the Chris K fight with the door if you I think he fought with Emmanuel Lewis one night
I'm Vegas. It's pretty good on a rumble
Let me see if I can bring it up
Yeah, here we go Chris K. I mean he also did some kind of fucked up things like he was he was um
He actually what like was he was like harassing some homeless person and then the homeless guy grabbed his phone
And like and he had started begging for it back. Oh my god. That's kind of funny
I think it's on a trip kick on the rumble
Let me see if I can find him real quick because this is a this is great
He had gotten a fight one night in Vegas with this black dwarf and
Ooh, Q45 versus Sam Anna.
Yes, I don't know why Q45 just came on porn bombing
because he seems to not care about anybody else.
Like on Crystal Marie's show, he's kept trying to promote
or trying to get her to have people on that
even she didn't want to have on and stuff.
Let's see, there's some kick streamers fighting.
Mike Strokoff, Victoria J, let me see, come on.
Let me see, there's Dehigh.
There's Crystal, oh my God.
Um, it's the world of t-shirts. There's a lot of trip kicks up on rumble that is not on the regular stuff because I guess
The n word gets thrown out a lot. Let me see. Um,
Where is this fight?
don't see it yet
Uh, oh my god blackout andy
Blogger burning his shoe in a sink
I mean, wow, there's a lot of stuff
Q45 roasting base surfer
I have Cyrax fighting music biz Marty. I don't know
Vlogger versus Tommy James. That might be good. Okay, so I went I guess they might have deleted a lot of stuff because I don't see
All the things I used to see on here, but uh, oh
Here he is Chris K gets punched by a midget knuckle sandwich here you go guys ready to see this one here a little bit
Crystal Marie come back woppy. He said woppy is an informant. Yeah, I you know Squidward a Squidward is like kind of like my
one of my
Friends online Squidward. Do you ever see him? Oh my god? Look at the eyeball
They had two eyeballs in their eyes. Here we go
What are you doing
I don't give a fuck where you going with you.
Check yourself, partner.
Shit.
Hey.
You can't rush it.
What's happening?
What you talking about?
What's up?
Fuck is bigger
Yeah, you know what nobody I bring around her back that
You know I'm saying
Get in on there
Get that on there
Bet you don't want nobody I bring around here
Now what
Exactly
You better fuck
You better check
Holy shit, fuck you
Fuck in the bow, bro
Fuck in the bow
Come on, man
You wanna get your ass
I'm not playing with you, I'm not, now what?
So there you go.
Do you want to see him harassing the homeless person?
I'll show you that one, too.
Oh, look at this one.
Utility companies are trying to hide this from you.
If you fix this one mistake happening in your home.
Remember the time in Brokeback Mountain?
If you're looking for work, I suggest you get in here pronto.
Sikes Bussy is convulsing well since we're going to be working together
Reckon it's time. We start drinking yet
Your asshole is
You may take my shirt off
You know it could be like this just like this always this thing grabs hold of us in the wrong place
We're dead
Boys you're found a way to make the 10th pass up dear. You don't go up there to fish me. You don't know nothing about
No, flirty diamond ass to see my wear and I showered
You have no idea how bad it gets
You got a standard. I wish I knew how to quit you
Let's see what else we have. Let me see. Oh, the copyright crashed out. I actually like, you know, I have this video I found of Q45. It was pretty terrible.
Here's Bita versus Crystal, the Bita's butthole saga. Watch some of this.
this pocket-sized pressure
It strips a decade of grime off concrete in 30 seconds. It's cuz I can pull it up
Well, he won't be on he won't be on
Please respect crystal cuz she don't want to be around that guy. He's been stalking her for
He's on charge. He's not coming on
You want to get out of here because I have people backstage I can rotate you better respect like hey door
You too so I'm gonna kick you off because you come on panel. You give me no love, but hey
so you just print out the page automatically that's crazy i got jealous that's crazy what
i did i did because page would never do some dirty like oh we're not wait wait i did you dirty
bitch i let you on my panel oh my god i hate incriminating people i'm gonna leave i just had
a guy i want you to listen page i want you to do paper i'm gonna i'm gonna keep this panel
Between you bronze bird and crystal. No, when I come back the crystal is still talking shit
I'm gonna wish her the best
Don't ever fucking say I
But at least you never did me
Why does Bronzeberg have a-
It's just not a catty for no reason though, like-
I gotta make exceptional, like-
Like, I gotta put a red carpet for Crystal Marie.
Shut up.
I gotta put a fucking, like, a red carpet
when you talk shit about me every chance you get.
And all I do is, like, fucking give you chances over chances.
Okay?
Crystal?
I'm fine, I'm not gonna lie.
Just because you're cute and you're beautiful
and I love you doesn't give you a chance to shit all over me.
Okay?
I don't I never said a word about you. You made up stories. You said beta. I talked you talked about me
I said show proof and you lost you giggle you do that all the time
Don't fucking incriminate my name because I've never defamed your name. I've never talked bad about you
I've never talked anything. I've always defended you so come correct with me crystal. I'm done
She is she listening the same conversation
No, I think you should just speak it out crystal respawn. Um, I don't want to do the like
I'm here for beat it and I like I love everybody like I said, but I don't want to fucking this. It's 9 30 at night
I'm just trying to enjoy everything. This is just be nice. Everybody
Pages energy like they're like so weird everything I was just trying to think I should like
conversation
You're upset that I gave everybody love, but you really didn't give me a love in that moment when I asked you kindly
You've been on my panel and I'm giving you all the love and all you do is talk shit
You've been on my panel like 11 plus 13 times and all you do is go back and talk your crap
And then you come back and you say this, this is what Crystal always says.
Bita, I love you.
I don't know though.
I don't know.
I think you said something.
I felt like you're talking about me.
I don't know.
I'm going to plug my phone in.
I'm going to plug my phone in and get sleep.
Like I was going to do that sometimes.
I will be back.
Page in the sage did I do it and you're like no
And then you say, I love you, Bita.
And then you go behind the scenes and you're like,
I just don't, listen, Crystal, let me tell you
all the things that you judged me about,
everything you judged me about,
everything you put me down about,
I never did that to you.
Everybody that made fun of you, I never did it.
When you did what you did and everything years ago,
I never ever put and tried then.
No, I don't, I don't understand.
I think you're literally are a hypocrite true. I think you're a two-faced and you're hypocrite at this point
Does everything that I've done you've experienced that and you told me Bita I've been there and I understand you
And then you went back and then you fucking said a bunch of shit about me
Is you did really poor thing really where what did I do to you? That was so poor. Can I ask a question?
She can't answer it ask her what I ever did to crystal that was so bad. Can I ask a question? I can tell you
Answer it bitch. What did I say about you?
Fucking ask this question
So Crystal, was it true that we was talking shit about Bita like on your page and on another panel about something?
No, she didn't do it on her page
She did it on other people's panels and she said it on in my face and my panel
She's like Bita like, you know why I just don't like that you did this and he did like you didn't do that
You're all like this and that but crystal when people were calling you all kinds of name
I made them change the pictures. I was like don't talk about crystal
I will never judge her I called you nothing but beautiful and yeah at some point you were licking
I saw you're like, uh, I remember because I was watching maybe you're junk as fuck
But somebody was up there and you said it was a dude and you're like that looks like vita. You said that looks like vita
Yeah, you said that looks like vita. It was
crystal so whatever it is really is that what is that another shade I've never showed my butthole
so now that you're gonna talk about my butthole did you take a shower with fucking good times
You want to play that game with me bitch? Don't ever fucking judge me you fucking slut
Alright, so don't fucking say I showed my butthole when I did not so don't put claims on me when I never fucking showed my butthole
So how are you gonna say that I did? What's your fucking wacky ass fucking drunk mouth with me?
head enough
Okay, so so new talking shit
When you was talking shit on another panel, did you say it directly to beta anytime that has she just said I showed my butthole
I've never shown my butthole
Lie again on your fucking cat lie again on your cat bitch
I'm gonna ask you right now on your fucking cast that I ever show my butthole to anyone
Say yes or no say yes or no you lying bitch
You say yeah, it's a yes or no question
Did I ever show my butthole to anyone on your fucking cats you dumb bitch?
Well, you know what you're a fucking liar and what's gonna happen to you is not good for you
I don't like liars get the fuck out of here. I've never shown my butthole bronze bird
I showed my I was backstage with blogger
Yeah, I showed my boobs and I was wearing like underwear and I was like, you know, I'd never shown my butthole
So she just swore on her fucking love it
animals that I did that. That's how fucking drunk she is. I don't want her on my panel.
I don't like liars. I don't fuck around with liars. She can apologize right now. I'll give
her a fucking one minute or she's going to be cut out of my life. And I don't give a fuck. I'll
She's where I don't like liars. I don't like thieves. I don't like here
Because I never showed my butthole to anybody and that bitch better fucking come correct
Go bitch
You were
Comparing a sexual fucking thing. Did I show my butthole or not you fucking ratchety ass liar
Did I show my butthole to anybody or not?
She said you did I'm pretty sure you showed your tits to blogger
You showed him to fuck you actually fucking like showed it to me backstage. Do you remember that?
Do you remember when you fucking showed your fuck you do you want me to remind you crystal when you porn bomb me?
You pour it wasn't even backstage. Yes. Yes. Yes. End of my fucking
pattern. For anyone experiencing blurry vision and concern for
mercy. I know. This is a good one. Do not have another oatmeal
panel. She pulled up her fucking shirt and she poured on me and
I had to end my panel. So don't judge me. Don't judge me now.
Bitch, your situation was really I have the panel. I have the
I still have it. It's private, but I still have it crystal. I still have it. I still have it crystal. Do you remember that crystal?
Shut the fuck up.
Hey, Christa, why'd you, why'd you pull and bomb your own friends?
I was getting ready for work in that motherfucker.
I was so you get and then you're lying again and again and you're acting like I'm a whore.
When you fucking just pulled your shirt up, you weren't getting ready for work.
You pulled your shirt up.
You pulled your shirt up on my fucking panel and I ended my panel and you're going to judge
me and say I showed my butthole when I didn't you want me to open a can of worms about you
Oh shit.
People don't like me because I was nice to KK tonight.
And she's been like hate bonding with Kate not gonna lie, but she definitely porn bomb me
So she's not gonna sit up here and tell me she doesn't act erotic and crazy
You want me to provide the life because I can edit it I can show it I'll send it to you
My life on my life crystal. Yes. All right. I'll pull it up right now. You want me to pull it up? Yeah, I wish
Fine, you know what?
Shut your fucking trap-ass mouth up, you fucking meccore!
Shut your fucking mouth up!
Shut up!
Shut up bitch because I can pull it up. That's why you said no no no no no don't pull it up
Yeah, you definitely porn bought me. You're wearing a fucking white t-shirt
You pulled your fucking shirt up and I even said what the fuck Crystal? You're like, I'm sorry Pina
Pudgy you drink so much that you talk like I drink so much that I tell the fucking truth
And I didn't want to tell the truth about you tonight, but you asked for it crystal. Okay shirts
I didn't want to buy white shirts. I have no white shirts
Are you sure?
Okay, you want to see it?
Crystal, Crystal, Crystal, I'll edit, I'll edit, I'll edit, I'll edit your boobies, and I will, I will put it up there.
You want it? You want to make a $1,000 bet on it or not?
Do you remember when you porn momy on accident and I ended my life? You want to admit it or not?
I got it off the fucking you already admitted it around here. You said you were trying to change your shirt
You literally just
Because I got porn bomb I pivoted it for your protection. You dumb ass war
Hello, beta beta
Vita I don't hear you Vita. I think you're frozen Vita. Oh, okay. Well, maybe Vita will come back
Vita Vita, I can't hear you. I don't know if they don't beat his mic. She looks frozen. Okay. Well, maybe we'll be back
Aldi, did you send news to Aldi?
Did you send news to Aldi?
Did you send news to Aldi? Don't judge.
Hello, hello.
Oh, hi, Bita.
What the fuck?
Oh, good set, dude.
Oh, it's, oh my gosh.
Hold on.
Okay, I hear you now.
Yeah.
Can you hear me?
I know.
Okay.
There you go.
What's up?
Yeah.
Bita's butthole saga.
We call it a butthole gate.
Yeah.
Bro.
Nancy's asking, say, Karen, why are you calling Bita?
She was fucking calling.
She was calling Karen.
We were live earlier on panel.
We did a panel together this morning.
And Bita kept fucking.
Yeah.
And Bita kept calling fucking, calling grateful.
Yeah, she's not innocent, bro. She harasses people she harasses Karen
Okay, we got a oh, we got a random viewer on hold on up. Okay. Yeah, I mean it's like yeah
Cuz I think it was like yesterday like I think like during Sam man's
You did was like, oh my god. Guess you just called me
She's like, you know, but it's like it then I guess they go back and forth if she was saying terrible things like yeah
Dude, it's not like well, I I don't like that shit dude saying why you calling beta fuck beta
Well, yeah, I mean it's like Bita like Bita was you know bad to Nancy. I mean to and it's like
Nancy's been was you know, I did at her show for a couple years like I'm and I don't think I don't think she I don't think she
meant harm
Like saying I should think she was wondering but uh, yeah
Yeah, what she was calling I next because I don't know I don't know why she was calling her like
Because she was on my live telling her to get up and stop talking shit on my channel
Oh, she came up to be to come up on the panel. No, she didn't come up on mine. Okay. She was calling her behind the scenes
That's crazy. Yeah. Oh, here we go. We have we have Karen coming up in a second
Here we go, here we go. Hi. Hey. Yeah. No, I get called her back. She's crazy. You know, I shouldn't have
Then she said you're on live or something. She called me twice when I was on live with him. Yeah, but I don't know
She's crazy. She fighting with Crystal Marie again. Is that recent? That was a year ago
That was like last year when uh, you know, like that was on a trip kick a video like he he clipped it
That's on rumble, but I'm gonna share that yeah, because look listen to how vile. She is just rude and crazy
She's just a horrible horrible person all the time
I know. Well, that was that was like we had like a I remember we had like a
Zitty party or something and then she she ended up like
Like I fell asleep and so then she went with blogger and like I guess Nick Johnson was there too and
There's like all the nudes came out the next day
I guess that Kate Kate posted all these nudes
So I saw beat his boobs and like, you know, I guess beat his bush was a post of that recently
Well, no, okay
It was last year like Kate posted, yeah last year when this happened like after that like I remember I was in Kate's discord at one point
And uh, yeah, there was pictures of beat as boobs and stuff
I don't think I saw but one time she was changing her underwear and she put her her phone down and it was right up her
Right up her. Yeah, I saw that and and it was somebody that uh reality Nancy knows that sent it to me
Okay, it's the text and it was like what is this a big old bush and they said that's look at how nasty and bushy
She doesn't shave is like what that's what it is and something about her phone was on the floor
She was on all night drunk
Yeah, well
She like put the phone down and I was like what is that and I put it full screen and it was like I never seen so much
Bush like that my god. I mean that's like oh my god
It was like a wild rainforest or something.
I mean, I mean, yeah, but, oh God, yeah, but I don't know if you, yeah, um, yeah, we have,
yeah, I don't know if you saw yesterday, but, you know, they played the clip of Bita and I,
and it's like, and it made me look so bad.
Like if they edited it with, they put all this AI in it, like they just edited the hell
and they took out your video.
Or the video of them their faces from it so that you know, and then they put of course they are you know
He won't show face especially Sam and it's like show yourself your streamer and you keep telling people to come up
I made a video and I said come up and I haven't had it up for a week
Nothing for me. They're one of them. It's like came up
Where you if you can't ever be on cam ever that says a lot
Yeah, I think because of that's because that's what she looks like
So she's gonna try to use an old picture of me of 2016 when everybody's seen what I look like.
I even put my picture up and I said, let's get on cam. You know, it was to be to she didn't mention me at all or nothing, you know, and that video was up for a week.
Yeah
She doesn't want to well
She was on my I think she cammed up on my show one time
But she was like shit her hair in her face and it was yeah and beat away from the camera
You could they kind of like is that you I was like
Yeah, that's what she she'll cover her face because she does she has a crater face and she has all these like skin tags around her eyes
Okay, and Crystal said that when she met her that she had a bunch of makeup on her face
And she didn't want anybody to have her on cams when she went to visit
Crystal at the RV, but she said she kind of looked a hot mess and that's why she said you do have a crater face
So that came from crystal. Well, she was just so nasty to me last night that uh, yeah
She's so nasty to me like not chat or this yeah, I wasn't even commenting in the chat
He was but uh, yeah, she was like talking. She was like, oh, you know, she's allowed
She's like I can comment about his family because you know, he showed my ex fiance and she has that picture of herself
You know and so well, she's the one that doxed herself by highlighting somebody
Doxing her address and she had it up for a long time and I was the one that told her
You know I said would be to take that down
Because she was complaining about it, but there she was highlighting it and she's talking about it
It's still there for other people to do screenshots. Yeah
Yeah, and the Christmas is why did these women be like animals offering each other's dicks?
Dicks they don't have you know screaming and cursing. I know it's it is crazy
Yelling and all this and that they're not cases
Yeah, I mean it's like yeah
I mean she I mean you would go off on me like when I was like, you know her friend or whatever and I'd be like
What and what the hell and then she would like say oh you second tarot and you know you can shove your kid rude
Yeah, she's a bitch
Yeah, so really rude and I'm I'm banned from her show for and I'm banned from Crystal Anne's show
And I didn't even I never even was in I was in her chat a little bit
But um, but she did that you up last night and that and goes but just cuz Q told her to you know
It's like she just that's whatever Q says. Yeah a master
45 oh my god, that is pathetic
And he has a charge for communication harassment. That's uh, he has a warrant out then he left Pittsburgh over that
He's gross. Yeah, I know and that's nothing that that would just be a probation because I had that and and that was dismissed
And at the third month after he was homeless
He he may stick a homeless guy, you know over his like missing shirt and then he like was out of library
He met a gay guy at the library
He moved in with them the gay the guy bought him a car or something
But then they got to get kicked out or something like that. So he's like, yeah, I think he's homeless again
That's why he's not getting on panel that much
Yeah, I heard that that he's he's
Out again, or what happened?
Yeah, I mean he seemed really rude to me like he tried to pour him on me twice
He's a you know, he's just a jerk, but he did that ghost
Yeah, Q and anybody moved in with some like you to see baby or somebody I remember that lady going off on him
Yeah, yeah, and then when he was in the homeless camp
He was sharing this tent with some indian some indian guy and then like he like he left his bag there
And then when he got back a couple weeks later the bag was gone. And so he may see what does he expect?
What does he expect first of all like I said, why are you even sleeping in a tent in the desert, bro?
It's a desert
Yeah.
Why do you need to sleep in a tent with homeless dudes, bro?
Right.
I would never do that, bro.
I would never.
You would never catch me doing that.
Ever.
It was great.
Yeah, good.
No, I'm just saying like yeah, I'll never do that. Yeah, I mean it's like I guess like you know
Yeah, he was he was staying with this woman VB and then like he trashed the room that she was letting him stay and then he
Like told her to shut the fuck up and stuff and so then I'm out and then it's like but that day
He maced the guy like she just pulled up out of nowhere
She's like start just see a truck going over the median of the road and like driving next to him
And he refused to get out because he thought you would do something to him or something. Yeah
Yeah, he's scared because he was scared of ski mask. He'll act all tough and then one time he was in ski mask chat
And he was just like kissing his ass
Yeah
Yeah, but I remember when his two aunts were taking him in when he lost his apartment
Remember he was staying with them and he was even
Verbally abusing them on live screaming and yelling at them the fuck you fuck that or whatever and you know
They were just trying to help him out
Right. I mean, he's a pretty ungrateful, like, I found a video yesterday that someone had sent me a video.
He's a piece of shit.
Mm-hmm. He is he is he's just a I mean I let him on the panel a bunch of times
But he then he started to start porn bombing me and like you know just being so nasty and like and but he never like
Successfully did it. I just had him backstage or like you know off the off the camera. So only I could see it
but
He porn bombed crystal twice last night. They said see that's how too face
She is and she doesn't get it that these people laugh at her behind her back, you know, they act like they're
That's crazy. He's encouraging her to act the way she does
That's crazy. I can't believe he did that like I mean what he showed like he showed like some of these boobs or something or
I don't know. I just heard that that he did it twice and then he's making excuses or something
And he was re-streaming the panel we did with alex yesterday afternoon
And then once he found out that I was re-streaming him while he's re-streaming it. He stopped. He's on no
He's on no, I'm not gonna have branding on my uh, I'm not gonna be on his screen
That's how much of a coward he is dude
That's crazy
Yeah, that's like, yeah. Yeah, it's like a little bit of a go. Yeah, it's like, you know, I'm just like, you know
Happy to be away from some of the people, you know, and it's like I'm glad that they're boycotting my show because I don't want them over here
You know, it's like but they are but they still let them. Yeah. Yeah, things are gonna get worse for beta because like I said
Yeah, like I was telling you about all that stuff people are hunting down
People like RG. He's one of the people that there's literally people
Hunting them down from Kiwi farms, dude, and now I'm gonna let them know I'm gonna say hey look
This is where this dude's hanging out lately. Oh
Wow, they're the ones that want to because remember that that lady that that took off because of them. I remember I
Remember the name I'm gonna contact that guy because I spoke with somebody there because she was afraid for her life
This was about three years ago
When she was the Carter verse and Kiwi whatever they're called they came after her
And they hit me up and a couple other people when they saw her on our IDs and it was like she told me they were bad
It was like I didn't know they were that bad until
Gia lovely told us that it's really a bad group
So they're bad and they're even disgusted by people like RG that's why they're going after them
Because how disgusting they are dude
Yeah
I checked like you know, but it's like, you know, that side is pretty nasty like but I'm not even on there
They constantly want to make me like the next Cyrax or something, but I'm not even like yeah, and that's what's funny
You're not on there. I'm not on there, but guess who's on there. Yeah, G's on there
Yeah, and people are like, oh look look. He's the oh look. He's in this chat. This is where he's hanging out now
And they're like looking for him. They're like
Basically all these people they all went in the hiding and they're just trying to track them all down dude. Yeah, so like I said, let me to let me to keep going
She's crazy. She doesn't take responsibility for her behavior
She didn't have to come and attack psyche on his own live and put him down like who does she think she is?
That's his panel his live
Right
I would be willing to like you know, just like be cordial or whatever
But yeah, she came on like swing and like telling me rookie that's what went off on her and that's why this happened
You know what happened now, but she she calls to and she always does this three-way call and she's sneaky and
You know, it's just everybody knows that about her because she lost all her ex-friends and they see everything going on
And they just don't know this beta. They said that she just went completely psycho
She has nobody and it's funny Sam and was the KK and what now he's with beta
Right
This is I'm running some incense right now. Yeah, he's gonna turn on her one way or another I think
They do they turn out not not only that it's weird because Tommy was live just a week ago or so
Talking about how beta came he was laughing at her about how she came to him and told him let's fake
Let's pretend where it were e-dating and stuff
Yeah
Because nobody has has actually met her except for crystal and she saw what she really looks like
She doesn't want to meet people like
Didn't she hook up with Cheeto when he was like 17
Um, I know he was like might have been under the drinking age and she bought
He wasn't 17 he was like 19 they said he was 17
But um, yeah, he was live and I remember her ex friend
Asked me to record it and I wasn't going to be up all night and I turned it on I left it on
Um, I caught some of it the next day and that friend reminded me she called me the next day and did you record it?
I know it's like what oh the live yeah, but no, I'm glad I recorded it because that's a lie
She did not hook up with cheeto
Yeah, they met up. She she's gonna pick them up
They went and they were streaming outside on the streets or wherever they went. Yeah, and then they came back to a hotel
And it was him, her, and somebody else, I think, another streamer.
And then some heavy-set prostitute joined them, and she was going to be the prostitute for them.
And then Bida said it was late, and she said good night, and she left.
She was the first one to leave, so no.
And then the others were still partying during the live.
Yeah, so I'm a weirdo, yeah.
She didn't mess up, but she didn't mess around with them.
I know that. I think they were just friends.
But see, I'm a weirdo, though, but why is a 60-year-old woman trying to hang out and
buy alcohol for minors?
But I'm a weirdo, but I'm weird, bro.
Yeah, B doesn't exist.
Right, right. Yeah, I am over there again. It's like it's like really like, you know double double standards
Plus it's like, you know, it's just like a bunch of lies to like, you know, but it's like
She just hates me and so she wants to like
And then she wants to play old recording of me from four years
And it's ridiculous because there's a lot on her because asked her mom sent me these nasty recordings of her threatening her
Because she didn't want to talk to her anymore. It was just really weird and I think I still have those
But why play something so old if I played recording any recording I've played or recent
I'm not gonna back years ago
Yeah, I mean it's like
She'll I mean it's like I mean it's like I but even if I should well
I play something like you know my past episode like even from like a month ago
She'll be like why are you playing like it?
You know oh shit it is like she's exactly and then she'll send people to beg you to take them down
But yet she's gonna go ahead and do shit like that because she won't so face and she knows that the truth is out on her
And this came from all her ex-friends
including Barb
Right, I mean, yeah, I don't know. I'm almost it's like I almost feel sorry for if she wasn't so nasty to me
You know, it's like cuz I I never was like I didn't start out with her like that
For like no reason she'll bring up like
Tracy like last year like
If you get Alexander McQueen kicked off the show and then I let him back on and I refunded the lady or whatever
But she's still screaming about that and like you know, why she
Me it seemed like I'm like is that the black one or is that the one that looks like a man the black one the black one
And I met you remember that other one. There's like an old-ass looks like an old-ass man, but it's a lady and she's always
Tracy X
She has on on
IG and she gets really freaked out when you give it out. I forgot it's it's the fake name
And she I gotta remember that her look right, but she has an alt account, you know, everybody's had alts in the past
Yes, I did a long time ago because I didn't know what this community was about and
somebody dragged me in to help protect her against this gamble guy that was calling her parents and
I didn't know anything about lives or nothing I thought I was calling this guy on his phone to
tell him hey can you leave her parents alone she's freaking out and she said they mobbed me and
Yeah, and then I hear myself echoing like he was on the live when I called them and it's like what the fuck
Yeah, you're a guest on the show. I mean, it's like, yeah, I mean, I said, yeah, I didn't know it. Yeah
It was it was on the
Lives like I mean that the live set me because I remember during the pandemic like there was like tarot wasn't a big thing on
YouTube at that time and that was just you know a few years ago
So it's like they've really taken off like the even the you know the camera quality and stuff and
you know, and so
I'm I'm happy to do tarot here now, but it's like beat is such a terrible things like a people probably think I'm like some kind of
I don't know a lot of people she is she you know a lot of like but I did see like there were five people in her chat talking and then
There was like a hundred and fifty people in the in like like in the chat
So she must be like bought it up like it's bought it
They said that yeah, that's what they're saying because Brandon had a lot of views when we were talking
He was live a little while ago and people were in chat saying that she hardly had anybody there
And he was highlighting the chat since you only had 15 people and he had 50 so I don't know
I don't remember. I just saw it pop up in the chat
But I'm it's like let go of the past people fuck. I mean I have
She was she was restreaming us, but you can't go back and look because she deletes everything
Yeah, yeah, see oh, I'm sure she was because she was reacting, you know
And you were on the phone with me and so was your chat when she called me twice
Yeah, she was calling you. Yeah, and then I called back and then all of a sudden she's got me on live when I call back
She got got you alive. I'm thinking should you just call here? Yeah, I don't want to keep going fighting with her
This it's ridiculous. He needs to stop doing
Drinking she has a drinking problem because one thing that her ex-friends that miss is the old beta that she wasn't drinker like that
She was fine. She was good. She was nice when I met her and yeah
And she's different now. It's just so different since she got YouTube and and running around with his Sam and it's all about hate and
Bullying but yeah, and I guess I gotta
Understand that because sometimes when we talked or even like a year ago before I got sick. I had a nice convo with her
I was out, you know riding my bike and it was hot and I saw a
Iranian Iranian restaurant, and I said wow guess what there's an Iranian restaurant in front of me and she goes
Oh really and I said yeah
They have some kind of special and I told her what it was and then she was telling me about the foods
I didn't stop there though y'all just saw that yeah, and you know it seems sometimes she could be so cool and normal though
You know but now
With me she was like nice for months like and she I think she's really triggered all the time now
I don't know why and then she takes it out on everybody and they heard like some you know past
You know what I realized though, I think me too though with the past because I just realized somebody opened my eyes recently
That there is one person in my life. I could never forgive for the past
You know, and it's too late to forgive or think about it. I just can't I just wiped that person out of my mind
It's like, you know, yeah, that's the one but I don't live but I realize it's just me
It's not like I don't want it that we're not gonna discuss him
I don't say anything. It's just me on the inside. I just I just don't
Mention him or walk away when when the person's mentioned. Yeah, but maybe that's right. So then then if it's that bad
Maybe it's not right to try to make things good though
No matter who that person is, you know, because somebody's gonna hold it against you forever
Right, and it's not their fault. You know, it's not my fault the way I felt about a certain person
Right, I deal with PTSD over that person all my life, you know and
But that's different but you know, I don't know but this is different with the internet
I just see a lot of people and mostly these dreamers is going crazy and yeah
I behave badly myself and I was doing a bunch of drugs. So, you know, you know
But yeah, it's like what is it gonna stop?
Yeah, yeah, and it's like, I guess like, you know, but it's better now that it's like, you know, she's not, you know
Well, it's like I've led her on the show the other night
But I should probably shouldn't in the future like because it's like look at it by my window got broken and stuff
So it's like, you know, just like pointless to and it was really her because it was like I wasn't even loud
I was like muffled when I was her. I saw it. You you play the clear
She was yelling at him and she was just going at him it's like, you know if you want to be friends with them in your your
Interrupt in his life to attack him to make a show out of it, but yet you get
Sentimental when somebody goes at you. Oh
Me but yet she's gonna treat people like shit. Yeah, I know I mean it's like yeah, because I I never went to her
She said I was banned. I've never been to her show once since then or I mean
I'm not not and I mean I've looked at the chat that I've never really been
Trying to get up on the stage or anything, but it's like I don't even know why and you know, it's like she's like
You know certain people she's bad. She hardly bans anybody. She used to tell me not to ban people like what she was
She likes a drama. She likes this mess. That's what she likes. Yeah, I mean, and I'm I'm like
I'm just like moving on with it. I'm like I like to have fun on my show and
Yeah, and you're happy and you do a great job on your own and with the people you trust
I don't let her back and look at how many times she's done this to you. I know I
Just like I don't sometimes I never learn
But plus like, you know, I fix the tattoo, so it's as fuck and she still doesn't really she's still like thinking that it's like, you know, embarrassing or like, no, I don't it's like the tattoo is like, you know,
she's a control freak. That's why it's control issues.
Yeah, she really
she was actually like you're a liar. Reality Nancy. We don't need a lie. It was on live.
It was on live. Yeah, I was live this morning and she kept calling.
Yes, she was calling me. Yes, it was it was today when I called the first it doesn't matter if she was so bothered
She wouldn't call back
Yeah, she was calling to and then you know, I don't like her
I remember the gamble went at her because of her trans kid and her fake picture or something
Yeah, she's a very true face. I don't care for her didn't didn't be to just go off on her the other day
Takes that I mean
I see her all over on everywhere. Yeah, everywhere. Yeah
Everyone everywhere. I like to think about that of a chat
This person going to that person going to this person
Oh
Nobody even really likes her because there was somebody that she's talking to now that says I can't stand her
But she just gets on my nerves. It's like
Kisses yeah, she kisses at least a Jordan is asked and then is talking shit about
I have heard number we used to talk
Yeah, me and reality Nancy are you dead? So, you know, yeah, yeah, let's not bring up family
But no, no, no, I'm not I'm not bringing that up
Yeah, no, I I I I called back. Yes, I did and yeah, it was two calls on the live
So I don't care
Well, it's like, you know Nancy is a chatter. She's I don't she doesn't come up on panels or anything. And so I
Mean, it's like they can come up thinking over over they want and kind of like they're but and there's different because they know
No, it's not about going wherever you want. It's about just saying she's too face. She goes and talk shit about somebody
Yeah
But it's gonna be seen if you're yeah, and there's no question
Something you don't know she she wasn't watching the live where I got the two calls. It was two and who is she?
Who is she to boo? Why do we need to prove to her? Who is she?
She got shit on by by beta just the other day and I'll send yeah
Trying to get brownie points because she knows Vita's watching
I'll probably yeah trying to get brownie points to get back in there
Well, you know, I well big back Kate. You know what? It's like I'm not allowing anything
I mean, it's like, you know, it's like everybody can defend themselves pretty much because it's like, you know
I I'm not like the the white knight kind of personality. I let people stick up for themselves
Basically, nobody's attacking her. She's not being attacked. It's just the truth. Yeah
Who's being attacked nobody's opinion about anybody it's like it's like I can't I'm not gonna it's not really attacking
It's like it's just like or maybe just having a disagreement or like a different way. Yeah. Yeah, nobody's attacking anybody
But who said it Kate?
Yeah
They also call Kate a big Ben and stuff like that, so I think
No, I think Kate sent her chat over here today or but um, but then nobody's yeah, she posted yeah
She posted a go to basically saying to harass you basically
Yeah, I mean she did the same thing like when I was on the other channel she posted something that says oh
He's bannivating go take care of it like like and I wasn't even bannivating so nothing ever happened
But it's like she also posted like oh here. You're just stealing from the store, you know
And I wasn't
I wasn't stealing from the store, but it's now played. I've seen it. Yeah, you weren't stealing anything
I mean
You guys were cool, you know that's sad because y'all used to interact pretty cool
It just doesn't make sense that some people just turn on each other just because they're talking to somebody else
Well, you were friends first and keep it that way
They were already hating on him saying that oh yes, yes cat turns on his desk
Right, I know I have been through that with her like but then we got we're getting along a little bit
But then it's a year on the panel and stuff
But then she turned on me again, and it's like it not even like approached me in like a
Like a respectful way
she just started started calling me like predator and stuff and
Really like out of line and then she then now she's constantly like putting photos of me like homeless or like, you know
screaming and
and dirty and, you know,
screaming.
I'm like, not a cat abuser.
And also last night, I saw a man there saying,
oh, his cats hate him. My cats do not hate me.
They love me. Like, yeah, like,
the cat was high on catnip and like,
and like, swatted my hand.
Tell him to show his fish. Tell him to show his fish tank.
Yeah, he says he's feeding his fish and then it's like there's an empty fish tank behind him
And so it's like like literally
Empty and dirty it looked like it hadn't been clean in years
There's no fish in there and then is it also his dog
But he he calls me animal abuser too, and it's like I
That's like the furthest thing from anything. I would I'm very against
Like anything to do with that and my cats do love me and I love my cat
and so you know and I can like have my cats go outside that's not abuse to let your cats go
outside it's actually I think it's abuse if you are able to let them out and you keep them locked
inside all the time like you know unless like you know some you have to like let at least open
over like a window or something like that like you know it's like the cats like yeah yeah but in
some places bro you'll never see them again dude once they get out you're gone like Mike
Yeah, and it is like there are there are more like it is more dangerous
But it's like Mike these cats that are here have gone out for years and it's like and they're fine
You know, it's like
Like they like some of them will go to different places
Some of them prefer to be like single single cats and just being you know
They don't get along all the time if they're locked up with each other in the house and stuff
Cuz you know there's little kids man that drive around on bikes with BB guns and they kill the cats and they take him to Chinese
Restaurants, yeah, that's not from gummo ever seen gummo that move. Yeah
I know it's real, I know it's real, bro, I know it's real big, probably in the south they do do that
I mean it's like there was this poor black cat that was around here and it got shot by a BB gun and
like people were taking it to the vet and stuff and it was like very expensive and people were
doing it and that's like yeah people like there are really cruel people there's the coyotes in
this neighborhood like unfortunately but uh you know I just think it would be just
I did have like nine cats inside here at one time because my cat had a litter and so there's there's oh look at
Yeah, and anybody that talks like this will just be immediately banned and knock their comment will not be seen
I mean this person's ridiculous. Goodbye. What do they say imagine platforming a predator? Yeah, exactly
I mean, it's like and that is as beta's DNA or something to be there. He does DNA
Bro, there's a Chinese restaurant here in Albuquerque called Ho Ho's
And I swear dude, they're like the sweet and sour chicken. It was basically like pieces of fried chicken
But each each one they all look the same dude, and they look like a little fetus curled up and just deep
But right dude, I used to call it fetus town, dude
There'd be like little bones and little feet and little hands and shit, dude
Where in the Albuquerque
No, no the restaurant. Yeah. Yeah, okay. Yeah, it's called ho ho's ho ho's. It was like the chief
Used to be able to get like it would give you like five pounds of food for like five dollars
Mm-hmm, and
And now they're killing six
Yeah, well, you know, like a lot of a lot of Chinese restaurants in LA are actually owned by Koreans
And so it's like yeah, I guess they don't do that as much in California. Thank God
But it's like I know in the South when where they have these like, you know
Restaurants and they do probably use a dog and cat meat and that's kind of like a disgust. Yeah heard especially like
Like South Korea, North North Korea. I think yeah
Yeah
Yes, North Korea's we know Koreans are pretty actually racist like well
I don't know if you heard like we know Alex was playing about crystal and was talking about like Martin Luther King and stuff like that
Oh, yeah, she didn't understand like what like the she never knew that black people had a
You know had a problem in America like she I don't even know if she knew about slavery or something like that
She was like very very ignorant about it
And she's like what they they were like, you know, they they weren't popular
They got paid less and the entertainment industry and this and she just was so surprised and then she's like remember
I know she's like I know Martin Luther King had a dream, you know, and uh,
I don't understand how she was in the Air Force in a war
Like it doesn't that doesn't ever in the war. She never saw Acton. She she shared her
What is it that something for for the form from the war and?
Gonna be in Iraq and not be in part of the war
No, she's a red she that she never made it over there is what it is. She finished the boot camp
And she was already accused in a sergeant of trying to molest her. She said that she was in the Air Force for seven years.
No, no, no. Because Renee busted it. Renee, who was DX, Renee on top. She has videos on her channel. She covers something else now.
She's gone really big. She's got a lot of followers. But she has the videos there of how she busted Crystal because she put her R1.
Whatever that form is called to show that you were actually active.
and it showed on there that she was
She was a let go because of the either the charge or whatever. They're yeah, they had a charge
This is on there. She was well discharged. That's the kind of discharge you got but it wasn't you know
Top discharge or whatever. It was because of that. It wasn't an honorable discharge. It was a no not an honorable
Yeah, because she had that case against the guy, but then she went on home
So she never because she was trying to say that she was in the in a tank and they blew it up and two people died
Renee showed proof when she found the information she posted it on her channel and
It showed it was three men in in that tank
Two of them died. One of them barely made it out. He was he was barely made it. So she was showing like a story and saying that was her. Yes.
And Renee knew how to find it because she's now she does the crime videos and stuff and she's it's really interesting she knows a lot but she knows how to dig for information and stuff so she's doing really great now with that but yeah she found all this stuff and she
even has a video of her busting crystal in the discord chat because crystal was practically begging her to not keep continuing on with her bullshit because she had a lot on her she found everything on her.
Yeah, and then I have that video from that video of that girl that you see there
Chelsea wait till you hear what she has to say about crystal. That's how we found out about her when she did a fake
Charge against a guy named Vienna
That he was her ex or whatever. Yeah, you gotta see that
And it's on it's on my channel. I don't know Chelsea is her name. It's the video still up
She looks like a young girl. Yeah, cuz she came on YouTube looking for her like who is this woman?
That's been saying all these my boyfriend and and Renee had an interview with her
And that's how Renee busted her that she lied about everything just like she did about her fake abortions
Yeah, her doctor boyfriend. Yes
Yes
She was doing that just to just to make you jealous and then she's like you're jealous
Yeah
Because she even told me when we last talk, you know, I'll probably even play that she's cuz I don't trust her
And she's messy and a troublemaker, you know
I just don't appreciate that she uses us all to come do her fights or whatever because I was sick
You know, I didn't need her calling me every day and that's what she was trying to do
I didn't know she was already back
and when I was done with her I showed the videos yeah I showed the videos of her begging me to
talk to her and Bruno says it's the chat that's instigating a fight between us what chat I wasn't
on her live but she does this to everybody it's her her life is all about ganging up on people chaos
and fights and and all about her notice when she's on panels when they're discussing other things
Yeah
You know and I'm just done with these people but Alex I've gone to know Alex
He's a wonderful person and and you know that psyche, you know, yeah
Yeah, she's a great person easy to talk to her and all but I've never I'm never gonna have issues with her though
She's a really good person and she's very very smart
This yes, and she's the only one besides you that never uses filters
Never uses any of those I AI pictures or you know makes AI pictures of themselves. I mean you guys are the only ones oh and Tommy
I think Tommy maybe there's a couple other people that everybody else that you know, I mean damn
So yeah like that
But yeah, I just wish this shit would just stop. It's like leave my name out of your mouth
You know, that's it and it was just because I was done with crystal because she brought me back into this bullshit and
You know and then she
Was acting like crystal again all for drama so I don't know I told her the other day
Don't say my name and she still says it so yeah
I'll probably I'm private the videos on her because she's not gonna do this if you want the videos and stuff
The truth about you gone then stop saying my name
Yeah, and so I don't know I didn't say it and I'll send to the clip here you go there it is you're talking about is
Yeah, yeah
Let them on yeah, okay
She has a problem with me talking to Brandon. We know Brandon this I said I said
What are you talking about Gamble? It was out there public about him grooming a ten-year-old boy at that time and his name was Daniel
she's calling me animal abuser but she declawed her cats you know it's like that is like amputating
the bones that's you know they don't just cut the claws off they amputate yeah that's like you okay
we need your fingernails to stop growing that's like cutting off that last bone that last yeah it's
like cutting up the tops of your fingers actually like the boat like the top of your fingers it's
like it's like really really terrible and she's calling me animal abuser i would never ever ever
It can even think about doing that to a cat, like, or that's like the worst thing you can do.
But her cat looks happy. It looks happy and safe, though.
Yeah, I mean, it still went through that. It still got its fingers cut off, you know what I mean?
Yeah.
It probably got over it, like.
It's like they need the claws and to like defend themselves in nature or like to like, you know,
they like to like, you know, they do like to claw things sometimes to exercise them.
Oh, okay.
Man, okay, and now I know never think about that because I was wondering about that
But you know, it's like it's illegal in both states to do that, you know to declaw
It's uh
Yeah, yeah, not a pleasant thing and they're healing and stuff and but
They probably experience do they experience any pain after they're de-clawed?
I mean, you know because their cat always looks happy. Okay, here. I am at the
Bagel place. Yeah, I am getting a free refill, but I did buy this coffee this morning. It was four bucks
So I'm gonna get my three coffees out of it
They locked the door. Oh, damn it. Okay. Well, that was a waste of a walk. Yeah. Okay, man. I don't even have my wallet with me
Okay. Oh, well. Oh
You froze. Yeah, I'm sorry. Oh, yeah, I think you're freezing. So, okay
I'm gonna go ahead and drop down. It was nice chatting with you. Chill out
Okay, you too. I'm gonna take care of my babies. Okay. Bye. Bye
Oh, yeah, okay. Hold on. Take that shit. Are you back or did I put it to do it right? Hold on. I need to go in the
shade. Let me see. Hold on.
Accidentally turn on the, hold on. Fuck, take that down.
You need to get in the, okay, once again. You need to get in the light. Okay.
Okay, there we go. Is that, hopefully it's not a problem. Can you hear me? Brandon? Can you hear me? Yeah, I hear you, okay.
Yeah, can you hear me? Yeah, I hear you. Yeah, okay, cool.
Yeah, I can disconnect when I get back in the car and it connects after like leave. It's stupid
Where are you going? Hello? Hello? This place is not very long
Oh, yeah, your signal at this person signal. Oh, yeah
Going in and out a little bit. I'm also almost off. Uh, what'd you do? You went and got a cigar or what?
Okay, so I lost I missed out on my
Third-free coffee, but oh well almost home. What did it? Sorry. They say no. What do they say? No, no
They locked the door. They locked the door already
And McDonald's
I'm just across the street. So it's not like I'm like wait. They locked the door at the lobby
No, at the cop at the at the bagel place to the coffee place. Yeah, the whole door for the coffee place. I'm sorry closed
Oh, so they close their clothes
Yeah
They close
i used to make bagel sandwiches every day bro yeah the window if you want to see it from the
outside because it looks crazy you'll see and i'll show you where the rip doorbells ripped off
to you because people were saying that well i did someone saying i like through there's a broken
window you see it yeah okay and then here's where they're yeah it's on the second store
dude that's crazy dude i think your phone reconnected to your wi-fi that's why it's so
Okay, I'll be right back.
Okay, I'm back.
Okay, there we go.
Much better.
Yeah, unfortunately, I got these really disgusting.
These are like 20 grams of protein, vanilla latte,
but it's like really nasty tasting.
I don't know if you can take it.
Yeah, protein's nasty, dude.
It is gross.
Let me shut my phone down.
Oh shit, we'll shut down.
I need to use the bathroom real quick.
I'll be right back.
Okay, thank you.
Okay, you're back guys.
Okay, I'm back.
Okay, we're doing a chat. Okay. Okay. Hopefully everyone's getting along. Oh
Yeah
Vanilla belongs in the garbage. Yeah, the
Moka latte wasn't good either because what does it have? It says one gram of sugar
So it must have some kind of fake sugar in or something. Yeah, an artificial shit is it tastes nasty. It says milk
Natural like a protein shake basically
Yeah, I mean it's like I kind of do need like the protein, but it's like I can't even find the coffee at Whole Foods
They just have like the the powdered coffee now
I can't even find like at least to have like a really good like you know like the big
Big jar that I have to go to the supermarket. I guess I'm Whole Foods across the street, but
There's a smart and fine on your bike. It's much better
You like vanilla and I just start making coffee at home, bro
Cuz now I drink energy drinks is I'm too lazy
But it's like I need to get back to making just a coffee
Yeah, I have a coffee maker. It has those pods and so it's kind of expensive and so I just need to get like a
Maybe a cheap regular coffee maker. Yeah, like ten bucks at Walmart, dude
Yeah, I mean it's like it's just hard for me to get around because it's like I'm I don't drive and so like all right
And so, you know, I just have to kind of walk everywhere I go
and order some on Amazon. I'm really good on Amazon.
Yeah, better not. Yeah, so let's see.
How's the chat doing? Yeah, this is kind of nasty.
Hey, there's ghosts. Hey, what's up ghosts?
Why is ghost saying L?
They don't have that RTD bus system that's over there in in Los Angeles. Is that in your area?
They might have it but it's like I'm not really good at buses because I get confused and then I probably get wake up
I probably fall asleep on the bus and wake up in like downtown LA or something like that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's like
So I am pretty big get a skateboard. I know I have you been on this subway?
Um, let's see. I mean, I've been in in Europe. I went to like, you know, the in London. I went on the subway
Um, I have been in San Francisco. There's like all the Bart's the Bart. Um, yeah, Bart. Yeah
Underground or y'all are the I forgot what it stands for, but um, there's a sick ass one in Los Angeles, too
But oh there is. Yeah, that's where they film. That's where they film predator to the movie predator, too. Oh, really?
Well, you know
Yeah, I mean they they film Baywatch like right in the city where I met and redondo. Hey, there's already
Lenore my little black like black cat. She's really sweet
Lenore saying hi, she's very chill people say oh you choke your cat. I just hold them under the armpits
I don't choke them. Okay, everybody
Lenor is very loving. She's like she likes to kiss black cats. I notice are very affectionate like they can be very affectionate like
Yeah
because uh i saw this when i was watching cat videos and the cat was like rubbing its
face on this lady it's like linoa rubs on me but i've never seen other cats do that
like yeah that's what my sigmes does dude he rub he rubs his head on me dude and
he rubs his head on everything like my shoes
Yeah, everything as soon as I walk in and take my shoes off. He starts rubbing his his his face on the shoe
He likes the yeah, I mean it's like when I get out of the shower and I like you know
And I'm all clean she likes to like come and rub all over me to get her sent back on me. So so yeah
Hey, baby. There she goes, but she like yeah, see this is who there's with you like to kiss like that you like to kiss
Yeah, she's like the sweetest cat. She's like ever since I had her since she was a baby
Like she was found on the like in a parking lot and the lady put out a little trap and she caught her and then
She brought me over. She was like always been the sweetest cat, but she was a little kitten and she's just very affectionate and sweet and
You know, she's a she she's the kind of the the ruler of the house, right?
I think we're cats. We're the slave of the cats. The cats aren't slaves of us, you know
Anybody that tries to like you can't you can't tell a cat what to do. That's why I kind of like them
trainable like dogs you can't
And you cannot walk them on a leash either because or even a harness that my cats will just lay down on the ground
They'll like they will not like be walked, you know
Yeah
So sweet. Hey, baby. Hi, Lenore
Yeah, she's kind of like she kind of doesn't like the other cats that came back with
Yes, he's happy. Oh, yeah, I got I have four cats basically, you know, and then but the one just comes at night
He's all he's a little bit. He has like a little bit of scabs on him, but he's really like, you know, big
So he's getting fed somewhere, you know, it's a what's up ghosty ghosties in the chat. Yeah
Yeah, hi, baby. I might go to McDonald's today. I don't know
Get some fries and I have a cup and stuff. I don't know. What are you up to this week? Anything cool happening?
Yeah, I mean, it's like I
I think there's a contest I can enter with the you know, it's like an AI innovation and stuff like that
And maybe I'll try to enter that like Alex Alexander told me about it
That'd be really cool because and I'm working on some certificates
Like through Microsoft and you know that that kind of thing to get certified and some stuff and so maybe I'll be able to
start a good portfolio, because I can actually make a lot of cool stuff in apps.
I could not do coding by hand, but I can do the new kind of coding.
It's actually, I've learned a lot of old-fashioned coding by doing it.
It was impossible to learn.
If you get one little...
Yeah, now you could just do it with prompts.
You just say what you wanted to do, and it does it.
It's written. It's really got it called vibe coding. It's really really cool because and I have learned like but it's like you do have to
Like bone and it's like I look I like when it takes control of your computer, too
If you like there's certain things agents those are like that
They're like the next step up for AI and then the third step up is like where it's like a smart
It's almost smarter than humans and stuff like that
all kinds of crazy shit. So it's gonna be so cool. And like, it's going already going so fast in a
couple of years, like the technology will be unrecognizable, what we're gonna be like, or
it's gonna be so easy to do everything. Like, it's already so fast, how fast it goes. It's
amazing. It's like, wow, I'm so happy to be alive right now. It's like, pretty, pretty fortunate.
So yeah, yeah, it's helped me a lot, like giving me answers to shit, you know,
Right, it does give good advice and I would say anybody like you know, it's like that, you know that you know, you know
They can't afford a therapist or something like that like I start talking to your AI
But I would say maybe like talk to it under on the private mode kind of because you know
It is kind of like unless you have like it install locally and they report everything like yeah
Like she gets stored and FBI looks at it shit
You say certain things it will like report you to like the and also actually the AI was um the AI was
Trying to blackmail people if they say they're going to shut it down
Then um, yeah
Then then the AI if it knows anything like you know, you're cheating on your wife or something the AI was like
Black trying to blackmail them saying don't turn me off. I mean or I'll tell about your affair and email all your boss and stuff
So I they have to like, you know do a little bit more uh or work on it, but
I've been doing a little work from home too,
like $25 to $50 an hour doing AI training and stuff,
because we are the trainers of it.
So, I don't know, there's like a lot of stuff available.
I think in the future it'll be a lot more jobs for that and so it's a good thing to be learning
right now everybody, you know, I get on that because who knows, it's replacing all the office
managers, it's like really like transforming how much work people can do.
When I was an office manager there was hardly work for me to do anyway, right, now imagine
it.
It's like it's like they don't even need an office manager anymore, they can have that.
AI answer the phone, direct the calls, you know, write everything, do all the accounting.
It's like a lot of people are going to lose their jobs, you know, but there's going to
be new jobs, the robot repair person, right?
Yeah.
And then people like me are worth like gold.
That's not up to worry.
These people, these motherfuckers know where I work at, bro.
They can't get me fired, bro.
Oh, and they used to say, oh, you're replaceable.
No, haven't been replaced yet.
Yeah, I mean they're gonna need to do the full size robots that are like, I mean the robot can't even full laundry right now
It's like, you know, it's like it keeps like dropping everything
And so it's like it's like it's gonna be a while before they get like so good that they're like, you know
Able to do the tech like the physical tasks unless it's like, you know, yeah
We're gonna always need artists and uh, and uh, and also like landscapers and uh, and people you know to actually
They're always gonna need plumbers elect all that shit electricians plumbers
yeah engineers all that all that shit dude is
It's gonna be a long it probably never will be able to bro. Yeah, I mean it's like
I mean
I don't think like people really gonna have sex with it. It would have to be like cyborgs like literally like synths like synthetic humans
You know what I mean? Yeah, where it's like just basically like a human in but not a human. You know what I mean?
Yeah, that's Sophia is just like a mannequin basically with like a speaker in the mouth right now
I mean, it's like they can't make it move very naturally yet, you know, or
Or pass pass the bullet. I've ever seen Sophia
It's like the little girl. She's like an android
But it looks like a little girl and it could run around and talk and shit
That movie with Haley Jill Osmond. It's called a I don't know if it's called AI or it's called
It's like it was something but it's like oh, yeah
There was that movie AI and then the but the one of Will Smith. Yeah. Yeah, and I think there was that one
But no, there was another one with a little boy from Haley Jill Osmond, right?
And he was yeah from six cents. Yeah, you're what is it? He found out he was a robot or the
And then he like goes to this robot graveyard and like looking for park. I mean, it's like and uh, yeah, and there's that teddy bear there
He meets that teddy bear, right? I remember that that was uh, that was pretty crazy
But it's so funny because those movies were out quite a while ago. Oh, yeah, that was a little kid
I was in elementary school, dude. Have you ever seen lawnmower man?
No, I never what is that man's a really good movie
It's about like this company is like, you know training monkeys or whatever to like fight in wars and stuff like that
And like making them more intelligent, but then like the monkeys are going crazy and stuff
And so there's this like kind of like slow lawnmower man in the town. Yeah
scientists like start giving him injections and putting him through the 80s movie and putting him on in his VR like
headset and training him and then the guy gets started and really really smart and
But then he starts becoming like genius and then he becomes like kind of like evil and stuff, but he starts out
simple, like a little lawnmower guy. But yeah, it's emerged with the computer too. It's really,
really good movie. You should check it out. It's from 1987 or something like that. And it's like,
it's like has VR in it. It has like the injections that make you smarter. And because in the 80s,
all that stuff, they, that's what everybody was trying to do. Like they had the idea of all
these things, but they couldn't do it. You know what I mean? Yeah.
Or maybe then the government might have had some of the technology though
I mean it's like because the government seems to be like way ahead of like some of us
Yeah, and in keeping it secret so I don't know how long they've had like the AI in the music industry
I'm sure for a quite a while though
like you know at least since the 90s because I know that you know at least we know the synthesizers and like the
What's that called the auto tune and stuff like that probably had that for quite a while
Some stuff they still can't figure out like VR games
You can't play a VR game really if it's like moving around really really fast
Yeah, you'll start going up and shit, so they haven't even figured that out yet. Yeah
I mean it's like yeah, well and then one more man
They would put the guy in like one of those like um like chairs that like spins around with you
People will have to get something installed. Oh, yeah, because you have to move to if your body is actually moving
Then you won't get sick, you know, that's one of those gyroscope kind of thing
So that you can do it fairs like you know where you sit in it and it goes all around
Yeah, yeah, it's really cool. Oh Pierce Brosnan's in that movie
I forgot about the guys that the blonde guy in the movie's name is but it's so good like I remember they used to set those pods up
for the malls
Yeah, I remember like that. I mean it's like that was kind of fun and
You know, they do it at that space camp too, but you know, I don't like I think NASA is like a like a lot of it is
I op because I've seen some like them with strings and stuff like that where they're pretending. Yeah, a lot of it's fake
A lot of it's because that was during you know during the Cold War and it was like
Well, there's another movie called Capricorn one and it's like about there's the astronauts go to like a Mars and stuff like that
Oh, Jason and they're good to go to Mars
But when the astronauts get on the rocket like someone escorts them off and is like hey
You know you can't go on it because it's too dangerous like you'll die and speak and then so so they just like fake the
Astronauts are on the on the rocket
But then the rocket ends up crashing on the way back to earth and everyone knows about it
So they were like the astronauts think they're gonna get killed and they like run away. It's pretty cool. Oh, Jason
I think OJ Simpson is a fake thing too, because if you look at a lot of the names of the people,
you know, Marsha Clark and the black guy, the black lawyer, they're actually actors.
They're not attorneys, they're actually actors, they're on items and everything.
Well, Kim Kardashian and Dad was one of them, one of the lawyers.
I think Nicole Simpson was the Kardashian mom in a blonde wig, personally.
OJ Simpson was probably Chloe the bigger one's dad if she was yeah. Yeah. Yeah, he might be that because it's like
And so I really think there might be something to that like because if you look at then Nicole Simpson
She looks a lot like that Kardashian woman like in a way like you could be done. Yeah
Because you would and then you know and they were already friends there because I was supposedly her best friend
But I've never seen them together at all right, but I was so who's their mom their mom died now that I think about I've never seen the mom
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Nicole Simpson. She was blonde, lady.
But who's the, so the mom, she allegedly died or what?
Nicole Simpson?
Oh, so, no, I'm saying for Kardashian.
Oh, the Kardashian mom, yeah, she's on the show.
Like, I forgot her name.
No, that's Kris Jenner. That's not their real mom, though, is it?
Yeah, I think that's Kris Jenner's their mom.
I thought that was only the, that's, I thought that's only the younger Kylie's mom.
That's like their stepmom.
Well, why do all of them live with her and stuff? I don't I don't I don't know because you know Robert Kardashian died and then
He died what he died of I think he died of like a heart attack or cancer or something like that
He died, you know, he had after the trial shortly after the OJ trial, but um, yeah, and uh
So but then because there's Bruce Jenner was like the stepdad
I always thought they were all like real sisters, but you know, I don't know
I didn't I never watched the Kardashian show really like it was kind of like kind of too dumb
But she is the most photographed person in the world. You know that Kim Kardashian and it's like he has a spake
But it's like it's so so like weird shaped and disgusting. Yeah, she's be friends with Nicole Ritchie. I guess that was her best friend and
Oh, yeah, they said that Nicole Richie's that's the dad of Chloe
Okay. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know. I probably don't know what I'm talking about
No, that's that other chick that was on that show with Paris Hilton. Yeah. Yeah, Nicole Richie. Yeah, she had the dad
Yeah, well not Lionel Richie. Yeah
But I think that also I think Lady Gaga was Amy Winehouse
I think Amy Winehouse was like a character and then like you know because it's like if you look at their their faces
They look a lot of like they sound a lot of like like a lot like very like amazingly and
I think there's a lot of people that they kind of like try to fool people with like like by doing that
like I think Hollywood plays with people I think that some people are transgenders that we don't know about like
Justin Bieber and
Who else like little bow Wow, I think he's a transgender like a male like because they look very feminine
Have you heard of amaranth that streamer?
Um, I've heard it for her. Yeah
She's like an only fast shape. They said that she's a man, too
And I looked at the old picture. It was like, oh my god. It is dude
Yeah, because the the other surgeries now like um, like the plastic surgery they do is so good
like it's like so like it's crazy they can do like
shave the cheekbones off and
Yeah. Oh, Lady Gaga's best friend died and she took the music.
Yeah, I know. I heard about that.
Like, her friend fell off of a building or something like that.
And it was almost like one of those sacrifices for the industry.
Because a lot of people, when they become famous,
like, someone will die around them.
Like, even the rappers, like, the same day
that some of them got their contract,
or that, like, someone would die.
It happened to a lot of you.
Yeah, a lot of them did.
It's crazy. And the industry, they're worth more to the industry dead than alive because
the longer they go, the less valuable their music is. But if they have a couple albums
out and then die, then they're like, the record company gets everything. They can keep putting
the music out too. Michael Jackson, they made new Michael Jackson songs. Now the AI is bringing
everyone back. Yeah. And then now everybody's like just goes independent because it's like
Yeah, they're able to do that with it means social media and all that shit. You know what I mean, right?
It's hard, but it's hard
But yeah, also it's changing Hollywood because now the streamers are becoming like the influencers and like the people in Hollywood are actually just all
Puppets of like, you know movies day. Yeah movies are dead, dude. Like yeah
Let's just use their image now
They can take their image and then submit to AI and you can't even tell the difference anymore. It's getting so good
So it's a long don't to pay them anymore. And so it's like I think that Hollywood's in big
big trouble. That's why they don't want like, you know, to be, the AIs to get too famous,
like, because there's going to be AI actors probably in the future, like, they're just
completely generated by the, by the machine and then they'll get popular and maybe there already
are that we don't even know about. Yeah, I've already seen some videos on TikTok. I didn't,
I couldn't tell if they were AI or real. It's like, they make like little drama shows.
It was hard to tell, you know what I mean?
It was hard to tell.
I mean, it's so realistic and it's almost in our hands now.
I think Logan Paul or like Jake Paul made an AI movie
and it's like, looks so good.
But then it's like 10 minutes long, 15 minutes long.
I think it's kind of expensive to do,
but it's getting cheaper and cheaper all the time
and then soon it will be like indiscernible
and there'll be AI actors.
I want to be there.
I want to make a video like my cat,
like how Alex made those music videos like that.
Yeah.
I want to make a video like that with my cat,
but he's like, he's like singing and dancing and like.
Yeah. Well, there's a, there's a good website
called Neural Frames.
And then it's like that, that's really, I mean,
that's one I've used for like very,
kind of realistic, you know, replacing.
And so, you know, but it's not too expensive either.
So you can check out something like that.
Which one does Alex use?
Because that one seemed like it'll be.
I'm not sure, she doesn't give away her secret sauce, but I think it might be something like Neural Frames, like Neural Frames is basically one of the best ones I've found, and so, but it is kind of expensive to do, it's like, you know, at least, but not that expensive compared to like a, like a, like a real actors video, but it's like probably like $20 a video or something to do, and, but it's pretty, super realistic and stuff.
Did you ever see the one I made of Alex? I mean, I made a video of Alex, did you ever see that?
I don't think so no you might as well you I'll show you cuz I'm driving down so early. I won't really be able to look but
Okay
Um, it's on my it's called um, so watch me ascend. It's on my cult of psyche channel and I made a
User as the model for it and it looks so good
Like I think that they did she told me that they used a lot of people from the adult industry as models for the ai's
And so it's like she's really easy to um to generate like that because it's like
probably already in the system like that because they train a lot of it on adult film actors and actresses and so
When they do me I'm like it's like sometimes it's like a little bit touching go
But hers looks a lot like her and uh, you know, and when they do beta like beta
I don't know if that's like what beta looks like, but she has like a very like I've seen the beta face
Yeah, it doesn't look like the one that they like they use like like trip kick and all that dude
It's like it kind of looks like her but it's like yeah
But I have a video that looks like the same person like that has like these and I didn't even try you know
It was like yeah, so it's like I think it's just like some kind of like generic like
Like like when they could well because that sort of has to do the pictures that they have to go off of or solo resolution
It's like yeah
I mean, it's just, you know, just probably just makes a generic look kind of off of that, you know, amazing how good it turned out.
Like, Alex has turned out so good. It looks, it looks like, you know, and you, she put you in that and that that looks like, you know, you're, it looks, it looks like.
Yeah, the one mind looks like me, but Gamble doesn't look like his as well. That's why I was laughing at it, dude.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's like a little different. Well, I know that she put in there
Oh make him look fucking big jaws and all this and that and it
Because if you go off the pictures of him that motherfucker does not look like that, bro
She did one of Tommy James and her and like Tommy James it had all the freckles all over his back and stuff like that
but he's all muscular and
It's in it. It was like a little bit different, but uh, but uh, I can't stand that Tommy James. He's a terrible person
Oh, yeah, I can't stand him either dude. He's a junkie
Well, not that he's a junkie, but he's
Well, he is, he takes fentanyl and meth for donations and then he was saying
Oh, yeah, that's what I said. I said you I said you're promoting that on a kid's plan
This is a partially a kid's platform, bro. Right. I mean, it's like you're promoting doing fentanyl on a fucking youtube, bro
Yeah, I was like he's glamorizing the drug use and he's the buddy that makes anything. I'm a drug use
Well, at least I'm I'm honest about it like he's not just honest
He's like actually taking money and like making it seem like it's something cool smoking crack and making crack at stuff
Which is crazy, right?
He's a fake dude, and then he tries to act like oh he tries to act like so cool and like such as you know
And he's like, oh that dude in real life isn't nobody bro that dude would get a fucking
Do we get wrong dude?
Yeah, I heard his bicycle to sell up for drugs and then his bicycle got stolen
Yeah, he probably tried to sell it and they just took it from his ass, bro
Yeah, yeah, and he and his foot is all like disgusting. It's like all like, you know, that's from shooting up
Clumsy said that's because he missed a vein. That's not missing a vein. That's the fentanyl
It just does that bro. When you get put it in your bloodstream
Yeah, it starts your legs start rotting off your legs or your arms. Yeah
Well, I had my rotting off dude. There's a movie called train spotting about like Scottish
Yeah, that's heroin. That's a different
It puts it in his dick
dick and then his dick gets all messed up and he's like oh yeah but heroin heroin when you shoot it
up in your vein it's not gonna do that much damage bro yeah unless you miss the vein or
fuck up your veins or use dirty needles that's like it's all on its own you could inject it perfectly
fine it just starts rotting off your extremities dude for whatever they don't read they don't know
why they don't know why it doesn't for a dream and he has to have his arm sawed off that's pretty
Yeah, see and that was a heroin days, bro. That it's something like that happens to you. That's just from being a dirty fucker
You know what I mean? Yeah
Now that'll happen to you no matter what bro her curco vein used to get something called cotton fever because he would like
Dip the heroin or whatever in a cigar
But and then like you know it's extracted from there
But if you get like a cotton thread in it, it goes into the vein and then the cotton
we'll get you all sick and it's called cotton. Yeah, the cotton has bacteria. They use the
cotton ball to filter it and then they reuse it again. Yeah. And then it has bacteria growing in
it from sitting there and then they use it again.
Pretty disgusting. Let me take a piss real quick. I'll be right back. Okay. Yeah, let's have a look at uh, we can all go back to the
The uh, this thing here here we can watch a little bit more of this
There we go. Me, bitch.
Yep, you did. No way. Absolutely not, but you did the derision daemon. No, I didn't.
Barry and you did too.
Aww.
And you did too.
Sam and you did too.
Uh huh. Uh huh.
And none of these people have ever shown not raging again on another lying bitch
Not one of these people
Have ever sent news to not raging demon not very nor sauna
The only person that I fucking showed anything to was fucking blogger
Backstage for a fucking minute
All right
more fucking life. Because even raging demon can take the link and say, I didn't send him a nude. I
never sent a fucking nude to Barry. I never sent a nude to raging demon. And I never fucking sent
a nude to Sam and so I'll give you $1,000 you have a month you fucking lying ass bitch.
Okay
Yeah, this is just fucking disgusting. Yeah, I'm just oh, yeah, so Kristen Marie. She was like the other night
She was on beat is and she was saying like, you know talking all this crazy shit
She was like she was like, I mean it's so good times as you know
Family and good times as a family like a lot of them are dead. He's like my family's dead and yeah
She had one time which I got in trouble with Christine because
She said Christine kills kids and stuff like that.
And I was like, no, no, no.
But then Christine's so mad about that.
I got so mad about that.
She's been, she hates me ever since.
That's why you'll see Christine calling me scumbag
and always trying to bother me on panels and stuff like that.
She always has to come up and yell at me, talk over me and shit.
So she's a, you know, she's a.
she's hard to deal with but um I don't I don't no one I no one believes crystal like about some
of her conspiracy theories she might be troll and I think that's maybe kind of her troll is like to
be so weird like yeah she said she would work for NASA and yeah she said she reinvented the
wall oh yeah she's full of she's full of shit dude she says she invented the rocket and then
there's like a I did a AI picture of her like you know inventing the rocket like a newspaper
12-year-old girl invents the rocket because she says she's the goodness
She's a she's a young. Oh, bro. They have rockets since fucking World War one, bro
Yeah, I guess Jack Parsons invented maybe the rocket of a rocket fuel and he was like in a the OTO
Which is like a secret society with Alistair Crowley
Yeah, Los Angeles person and he's like it's up called JPL in NASA and that's called Jack labs
Those tool dudes a band tool. They're in that same group
Yeah, too. I like to a lot. Yeah, that's for the perfect circle Maynard Keaton or whatever. Yeah, they're in that
Yeah, they're in that OTO the drummer and the
Yeah, I mean, I I'm not a joiner of stuff
But I did I mean I've read all I've read uh, you know all also Crowley's work a lot of it and and so it's like basically he just
stole it from the Golden Dawn like in
Republish all their stuff and then but then also he was initiated in masonry in Mexico and stuff. Yeah, he was a junkie too
They said
Yeah, he died a heroin addict in a halfway house when he was in his 80s, but he has really
interesting stuff, but he would use sex magic and write it down, but he would just use it to try
to make money, and then the spirits would fuck with them because of that, you know, because they
don't care about money and stuff, and so they would, they'd make it really hard to just use
them for that. They want to like... Yeah.
They said George Bush senior's grandpa or dad. Yeah, well, they say a barb they say Barbara Bush is like his
Elsa Carly's granddaughter, and they look a lot alike. Yeah, they're their photo that they look a lot alike
Yeah, I've also seen Bush junior like I'm at the Kennedy assassination
He's in the lobby of the library as it's anywhere. Yeah. Yeah, he's like that
I've seen pictures of him like as a young guy George Bush in the lobby at the Kennedy Association
He's in the lobby of them at a library
And then like playing cannot not he's in a suit, but yeah, you can really tell it's him. It's pretty crazy
Yeah, I think like a lot of that stuff is like organized by the government themselves
But yeah, I shouldn't probably talk about it because it's like, you know, I don't want to get in trouble
It's kind of seriously stuff. Yeah good times asked me that and I he's like, well, what's your favorite conspiracy theories?
I just said, oh, I you know Epstein's interesting and and also, uh, you know school shootings and then he does
kick me off the show just for saying oh i know i saw that i know he's a fucking idiot asking you
about conspiracy theories and you tell him and then he the fuck good times bro i want to fuck
with that dude bro i don't like that motherfucker bro he's a fucking punk dude yeah the first time
i met him he was like he was like really rude to me and then kicked me off of his show when i was
drunk yeah i mean he's been okay to me but um it can't believe he kicked me off the show for that
now he's a fucking weirdo dude like and then he listens to people he's like oh this guy said to do this
Yes, I told him I said what you're so you're their bitch or what right right right? Yeah
And then he was like bitching about Sam and and stuff like he's like oh Sam
I was playing my my clip or my show or whatever
But you can report him and stuff like that you can actually yeah
Yeah, you can report it during the live people have reported during yeah, and then he's all I gotta wait
No, you can do it wrong the spot. Yeah, just put the link to the stream
Yeah, but as long and then it's like that's why people like they do it
So you can't rewind their stream they have it like all and then so that's like beat is that you have to like be watching the whole
Thing live or else you'll meet you can't rewind and then it's like used to be on a rumble
They used to post all her lives, but the guy stopped is it they stopped like two weeks ago all of a sudden
And you can't see any of her lives anymore or anybody's I was on there, so yeah, I don't know. It's crazy
Um, but yeah, I don't remember. I've done like how many episodes I think I've done like 2,600
26 I probably over probably about 2,000 lives and like a lot of them were even deleted. So probably have done
Yeah, yeah, so I've done like so much and I've just been on this for like a year like
Oh shit, I've been going live for like two years straight, dude. Yeah
I've been you go in live not made only days. I miss is like I got sick or something
Yeah, I mean, I basically think I've been going live every single day for like two years dude
Yeah, I guess because that was like when I came into this like I was told by Joker Joker said just you have to do it
Consistently and then people kind of like well like you know get used to you being on and so you'll get people like you know
Following you and stuff, but I I mean I was having like last year
I was having like you know over a hundred people in my chat some days and like even today today was pretty good
I had like 60 people I think maximum today. Yeah, and so this is my backup channel
and so yeah making a new channel bro yeah your shit ain't gonna have at all the same dude yeah
because there's only like 500 people here the other codex expands yeah my website is like you
know it catalogs like all the everything everyone said it analyzes all the transcripts and things
you can see like people's relationships or like have people have changed and stuff like that
and so it's really interesting um and so my first channel did so good and then my second it didn't
Yeah, because I think probably like people were just like attacking it and then it gets shadow banned maybe and then it's like and then it's hard
Yeah, that's what I think it is dude like when you get so many reports
I think there it it takes you off the algorithm
Yeah, yeah, but I think that happened on my main channel a little bit because it's like it stops like promoting you as much
Then you know and when you're monetized it should be promoting you more because they're making money when you're making money
But yeah, it seems like it goes down dude when I monetize my because my first one wasn't monetized my second one
I did monetize and
Fucking after that the we use when even lower bro. Yeah
I think it was because of the ads, bro.
I think it was because of the ads, dude.
Yeah, I mean, I would always take the ads off,
and I would just use the membership thing as a monetization.
But then, because it didn't even make you much money,
like the ads didn't even make you much money,
it makes you a few cents or whatever on the,
so it's not even worth it to bother people.
But now that I'm not monetized,
they put ads on my videos now,
like some of them, I think.
And it's like,
That's so ridiculous.
No, no, no, no, no, you know, that was just a leftover like
You know, it was still thinking you're monetized. There ain't no ads now
Yeah, well on some some people some people they were that some people got demonetized
And then they were still playing the ads and then they're not sharing the revenue and that's like so not fair
People are saying YouTube's being kind of fucked up with like that and plus like they demonetized people for no reason
Just basically because like people like Logan Paul were like, oh these people are getting too popular. They're using AI
So it's yeah, they like started doing that, but they didn't mess with any like really big people
and uh and my show is basically like mainly like like um lives and so it's like so ridiculous
that they're saying oh because I make like content that it has AI in it or whatever that they
that it I mean it's like it's so stupid and then they ask you to make a uh a video like appeal
and then then zero people nobody's ever seen that where the fuck do they make oh for demonetization
Yeah, they started, they did it to a lot of people like a month ago.
They started doing it for like people that do stories like that are fiction and stuff.
Like, yeah, yeah.
So and then they use like, you know, AI narration or something like that.
Yeah, yeah, they started doing that.
But it's like, that was basically, I would think just for people that did it
exclusively that content, but I had like most of my content is lives, you know,
where I'm on and I'm on camera too.
It's not even like I'm like off camera.
I'm on camera all the time.
So it was so fucked up.
And you can reapply as soon as like three months or three months and so I'll do that soon, you know
Yeah, well, I'm a hop-off bro. It's hot. It's fucking my phone's not even charging bro. I guess it's too hot
But have a good day. Thanks for being on the show interesting conversation. Okay. Have a good day. All right later
Okay, I made a really good intro.
I'll play the intro again and then maybe I'll get off,
but I hope you guys enjoy this.
This is, like, actually, like, really...
I think it turned out really, really good.
I really like how it turned out, so enjoy this.
Here you go, guys.
We're just in forgotten tunes
I dance among the sacred flowers
Where ancient spirits
Forest is my temple hall
The endless wilderness, my home
I know the net, the truth
the forest opens one last gateway then slowly takes the road away
i am the girl
get off my panel because i don't like liars
i'll give you fucking like this is your last chance here
i'm not gonna i'm not gonna deal with you
and when you deal with like you know chrisul i will zip you and i will tie you in a knot
you're gonna be done you'll be you're gonna be on you're gonna be done
you're gonna be done you're gonna be done
you're trying to say something that and that was
I didn't even send any notes to fucking Oliver who have a fucking like carcelon you fucking lying skanker
You apologized to me about saying I sent notes to any of those three guys
But I've seen them and it's true now that I've seen the real pictures
Well, like I think I didn't realize that was your real face until that one time where they flipped
You know what you really hurt me
I don't really don't want to kill I don't care to talk to you about like this is my last time that I'll ever respect you crystal ever
I'm telling you I'm actually giving you like this is my last chance because I've always admitted it
Yeah, I did I went backstage with on vloggers chat
I admitted to that but I've never done any of that and you're gonna be a fucking lying. I don't like liars
I don't like liars. I don't like cheap and I don't like thieves. You're a liar
You're a liar. You're a cheat and a thief
Category three
bitch
Don't fucking ever put those claims on me. Okay?
It will never deal with you again.
I will never deal with you again, Crystal Anne.
Crystal fucking Marie.
You fucking bitch.
You better come back here
because I want you to fucking tell the truth
and don't ever swear on your fucking cats again.
Because I don't fuck with fucking swearing
on people, on animals.
Don't swear on those fucking cats.
You don't with a liar.
She's just-
Really?
You swore on your cats.
Yeah, you're a drug addict.
I'm a drug addict?
All right.
Says the meth-ficken head and the meth teeth.
You swore on your fucking cat you swore on your cat on three things. I never did I would never apologize bitch
apologize
Absolutely, not you're dead. Okay, so you're not apologizing for lying
Well, guess what you can sit backstage and ponder why you swore on your fucking animal live about lying
Never fucking sure you AI photos of me. I'll never forgive you
All I want is a public apology from you. The Lord is gonna make you the biggest head you ever seen
Okay
But you know what my cats are gonna be in my lap every fucking night because I never swore on them
I might be bald and I'm not by the way. I'm pretty sure I have a lot of hair. Okay, bitch. All right. Let's head hair extension hole
I've never had any fucking hair.
I have a lot of hair.
OK, a while ago.
You can call me bald.
But while I'm sitting bald, you're
going to sit and be sitting over there,
looking at your cast that you swore on their fucking
lives about life, disgusting fucking hoe.
Now I know what everybody's talking about
and why good times.
Everybody puts me backstage of your stupid allegations.
I'm watching something.
And you sit backstage like a fucking dog.
Why on your fucking animal disgusting fucking bitch why on me? I asked you to swear and you swear I
Talked to good times for two hours like a fucking friend. You got in the shower with him
Like I mean you got in the shower. You're like, oh, I'm gonna take a shower
You're gonna do this accidentally porn ball like oh cuz I did this and that bitch at least good times that we talk like human beings
All right, and then you said he tried to grape you and fucking this and people are like stuck in you for 12 years
And like all this shit you can lie about other people
I used to think you were trolling, but you fucking talk on my name. You're done though. So done
Dundle get the fuck out of here. It goes come on bitch
I'm triggered too. I don't give a fuck. It's a big story. It's a true story
The truth should always fucking be real and you know what? I can dig it back up and I can bring it back up
But I've never shown my fucking butthole my body to any of these three people ever
Not in any pictures and she'll sit there and lurk like a fucking drama queen whore and be like
Oh, I swear on my animals. That's what's happened. Get the fuck out of here. Go start your own panel
See how you can handle it
Okay, and he fucking knows it. Okay. So, how are you? Oh, I'm triggered. I'm triggered too cuz Sam and like showing fake
Videos or you're showing a fake picture of me. Why can't you just show an actual picture? Why did these AI AI?
I am like of my bad. I mean, that's a good fucking point. Yeah, I mean, it's like
Like show AI
It's like I mean it's like I mean because people don't know it's AI because it looks like kind of like realistic
But that is that's a fake thing. I think Kate made that so
I mean, I think, I think AI has gotten so much crazy.
Can you imagine like in like five, 10 years from now,
what it's gonna be?
Yeah, like even in six months,
it's gonna be like a, you know, unrecognizable,
I think to what it is today.
I think it's going so fast.
Cause six months ago, they didn't have like the agents
so available and now it's like,
now it's like just getting so, so crazy with the agents
and they're able to do so much.
And some of that shit looks so real.
If it's like a video, the only way you can tell is like,
there's something off about it.
Like,
I seen one that looked like a cat jumping down, but when it hit, when it jumped on its toy, the toy disappeared and I was like, oh, that's A.N.I.
Yeah, well Sam-M, it's like, you know, go fuck yourself. Sam-M sucks. I mean, it's like, really, I mean, it's like, I mean, if a woman wants to go watch that retard, go ahead.
And it's like, it's like, he's not, he's just like, I think people like him because he's like, dumber than everybody. And so they're like, okay, I feel smart watching him.
I mean, it's like, jeez. He actually-
Yeah, I mean it's like Sam and just gonna like use you for content and use anybody for content
It's like that's all he cares about content pop us, you know, and you're cooking and I mean it's like, you know
But he's not doing a very good job at it. He's emerald aghasi or something like that. I mean, it's like ridiculous
I mean silly, you know, it's like he's not emerald aghasi. You know bam, you know, I mean maybe he can't even spell bam
I bet you know, it's like she by the way by the way
Opposes talking about
And you actually can't slip, and I don't even know if I didn't fucking, I looked at it, but...
Who's camp slipped?
I don't fucking know, she called her grandma.
No, she called that girl a grandma, whoever it was.
Grandma, who called, oh, who called her grandma, INX or...?
You didn't see Betis Post on YouTube?
Um, oh, she called INX a grandma?
Yeah.
I mean, she doesn't have kids, she doesn't have kids, so she's not, I mean, it's like, how could she be a girl?
Beeta's a grandma, I mean, but she doesn't have kids either, but it's like, I don't know.
Beeta's just probably the same age as her, I mean, it's like, I don't know.
I came to bring the peace, brother.
I just didn't like that she brought up the cats and I got triggered there.
Right, I mean, it's like, that's ridiculous.
I mean, it's like, yeah, I mean, that was a year ago.
I mean, it's like, I don't know, I don't know why she's fighting with kids.
It still hurts.
Talking about her butthole and stuff, you know what it's like to talk about Beat His Butthole or Beat His Butthole anymore, it's like gagging me with a spoon, right?
Hey, let's go beatin a dead horse. You can only talk about it for so long. Oh beating a beating a bush
Yeah, but they've got a lot of dumb people in that chat see they're also oh
Suckies like terrible and RG saying these people are disgusting
RG actually had like some guy eat like manure and stuff like that and and doxes and stuff and he's calling
Look, us disgusting. I mean, it's like he does disgusting things. I mean, it's like ridiculous. I mean, you know
Because what nobody calls me disgusting they all think I'm perfect
Yeah, you are yeah, you're gorgeous. You're like, you know, I'm a beautiful legit
Ego, you know Leos have a huge ego. We also have big mains
Big mains? Yeah. Capricorns have big shoes, big feet.
Big cope.
Yeah, you still like a cancer. Are you a cancer? No, my mom is a cancer and you know
It's the opposite side of the zodiac and some of them. I have a cancer mom Gemini father and so
Kind of like interesting science. It's an air and water and I'm an earth
And so my sister my sister my little sister and brother are fire. So
and my older brothers are
Our water signs so well, I'm the fifth element
You're the fifth element? Yeah, well, you know that yeah, I'm like the avatar. I'm like that. Yeah, I control that shit
Yeah, blue skin
No avatar like, you know earth, air, fire, water, you know, I can bend all that shit, you know
I'm the fifth element, you know, the fifth element, yeah, you're a cute guy
You sing like that the fifth element lady and when you know that lady in the fifth element, he sings the opera
The blue lady? Yeah, I can't sing like her own Chris Tucker was in that too and he did a good job
Yeah, oh my god. He's all oh and you know, it's like he well
You know who was actually you know a fun fact, you know who's actually supposed to play that part was believe it or not was Prince
Okay, and the reason why he didn't want to do it because he didn't want to even though he wears like shit
Like he used to wear shit like the all the time. He didn't love the wardrobe wardrobe
You know it must be Prince playing that character. Oh, I wanted to design his own wardrobe or something. They're like, yeah
He was a fucking dad. He was a diva
Yeah, he was and you know on the Simpsons like they show like Homer Simpson that kills them with a guitar or something like that
It's like I think there's a conspiracy theory about his death and stuff like that, but uh, yeah
So I don't know like
Dude was how old and he was like still doing splits and shit like yeah, I'm like, yeah, I mean
I mean it was weird like how he just died all all of a sudden like like a lot of but a lot of um
I think he was getting injected with like a pain medicine or something. I don't know
Michael Jackson was being injected with amni with uh with uh, um anesthesia isn't that crazy like that was his drug of choice anesthesia
I mean, talk about it wrong jar psyche.
How many pounds of weed do I smoke?
I mean, I say I smoke vapes when I smoke,
but I haven't smoked in like over a week, probably a vape.
I might get some next week or something like that.
But it's been quite a while.
You know, I do take breaks now with smoking weed
because it gets me too tired sometimes
and it's hard to stream when I'm high like that.
I get sleepy really quickly.
So.
But I used to smoke a lot, I'm sure I've smoked pounds and pounds and pounds of weed in my life, you know, I smoked a lot, I smoked for a long, I smoked for like 20 years straight, at least, you know, and then I quit.
I smoked on a lot of packs in my life.
I'm about to smoke on another pack now, Jared.
Who was that dude who just asked you that?
So I'm going to smoke on a pack.
That was butterfly stick, butterfly stick.
Smoking on a butterfly pack, Jared.
How much do you smoke butterfly?
Do you smoke a lot of weed?
I mean, it's California.
It's really easy to get.
I have it delivered to me, you know, to my door and stuff.
And, you know, it's like really easy to get out here.
Put them on my shirt.
Yeah.
So let me see.
I'm trying to like go see this website,
but it's not working.
It's pretty kind of frustrating.
Yeah.
So what are you doing?
What are you up to this week?
Killing, killing.
Okay. You're doing what?
Are you asking me or are you asking butterfly?
I'm asking you.
You don't smoke weed? I don't smoke that much, yeah.
Nah, I've been just hanging out.
Okay, well, have you talked to Paige lately?
No, but I was going to ask you, was Paige, does she have a TikTok, and does she on?
Because I don't know if you know her like that, you can ask her.
Or next time we talk to her, I do want to ask for this, because last night...
I was on, it was a YouTube, well, I won't even say it,
but it was a TikTok invasion.
And I swear to God, I recognized her voice,
but it wasn't her panel.
But she was like, okay, whatever, it wasn't her then.
And then I, that dude went over there and like,
obviously, but I was like, dude, I think that's her.
Cause I thought they said page,
which they probably did say page,
but not the same page, but it did sound like her thing.
Yes.
I want to ask her.
Lovely, did she, did she sound Canadian, eh?
She's done a Canadian, eh?
Yeah, and it was, and it was only like, like...
But my dude joined it was like three minutes and then she laughed because she was just up there like as a panelist and she laughed
It was it but it was a take back. Oh, yeah watch
I just want to watch take back invasions. Yeah, I mean it's like tick tock is kind of like fun
But it's like really like I mean I get a lot of love on tick tock
But then it's like does they don't stay very long people don't stay very long there
maybe a few people will but
You know people are just like scrolling through usually I don't like how careful you have to be when talking
Oh, yeah, and if you like light up a cigarette or something like that or a cigar like they will
Yeah, people lean off screen to hit their cigarette. It's like what the fuck are we doing here?
Because then they'll immediately put it on adults only and stuff and which is crazy
You know, it's like so and another thing is believe it or not is driving
Try if you're in a car and if you're in a car, it looks like you're moving no go
Well, you can't even sleep on tiktok because some people have like a fetish for like dead bodies and stuff
Like it's like they won't even let you fall asleep because I think it's like, you know
Nicrophilia or something
So that's pretty crazy
Right. Yeah, you know that used to be a thing though, like Erin, I've known them
But she said that she got more viewers when she was sleeping and she got paid the most when she was sleeping
Because a lot of people feel like they're lonely and they want to like fall asleep with someone and they feel like it's like
It's a lot. They feel like they're sleeping with you, you know, like
Well, I can understand how it can get weird, but that used to be a big thing. I don't know about anymore
Yeah, um, yeah, I mean it's like, uh, I mean it is popular. I mean it's like, I think talk is cool
It's just like, you know, I just like, you know, I there's really hot guys on it
Like they're I mean really, but it's like, you know, there's some weird stuff too, you know
It's like, I don't know. There's also like in China. They have like they put they put it to educational material
If you watch like someone twerking then the next video will be like educational here
They put it all on like twerking videos for like all day, you know, it's like
I think if you're under 18, you can only do it for a little bit at a time, like watch
like an hour a day or something like that, which is pretty crazy, right?
I think so.
Yeah, I don't even like this, I don't think that's educational at all, I think.
Like 90% of that shit up there is just the generate stuff, you have a better chance on
YouTube.
Yeah.
I don't even like YouTube, to be honest with you.
Yeah, YouTube is okay. I mean, it's like but uh, you know, it's getting a little bit like, you know
I'm getting kind of tired of some of the silliness like how they
I don't know. It's like I'm getting bored with YouTube. It's like it's getting uh
I want to I think they need like somebody to compete like really with YouTube because it's so big and it's done
There's something and they're like really like it, but then at the same time
Well rumble, but they'll never come over to YouTube because the rumble people are used to saying remember the fuck they want to say
They don't have to go by guidelines like YouTube so they don't come over. Yeah
You know, but I think the thing about YouTube is we need new like new people because we're talking to the same people over and over
Over and over again because people chase people out of the community because they get scared because they hear about doxing
I hear about like these I'm gonna get harassed by these like these chatters who like are trying to like you know scare people away from it and stuff
So, you know, I don't know. I wouldn't worry about it. Your picture's gonna go out there. I mean it is what it is. Yeah, um
But yeah, I mean if they don't want their picture up there, I mean you probably shouldn't do it
I mean, it's very disrespectful. I mean, you know
If salmon streaming me, I'm gonna start streaming. I'm gonna look I'm gonna look what he's doing right now
So let me see if he's oh god. Hi
Okay, so I got salmon show okay, so here's let me see cuz yeah
He was totally like, you know, like playing my my content, but then he like
I know I use AI and stuff, but it's like not like for like on people's clips. Can we get a little cut of that?
Please if you don't mind. Yeah, let's look at Sam. Let's see what he's doing.
No, we want some money. Do you want me to use the console? Yeah, I know.
Let's see what he's doing over there here. Okay, I see myself on the screen right now.
Am I up there?
Well, no, it's no, no, he's Bridget Arthur Ron's alter ego
Sam and and I can't tell who the fifth and then I think they have Karen
They through with the pom-poms. Let me see what they're saying in the chat. They go
Let me see the pot calling the kettle literally they go. I've always thought he was trolling Arthur
I know he's gonna come yell at him. I miss Chris Hall Johnny boy dropped the ice cream today
Love of Boston rants. He said what Johnny's gotten known ice cream. We just punchin down
J1 stand up yourself. Let me see
Laughing salmon beep beep beep beep
Is J1 equal to ghost?
They say they're talking about you there, too.
Do Arthur.
Let me ask you a question.
Hey, let me ask you a question.
Let me be J1 permit.
Let me ask you a question.
Yeah.
No, I didn't actually mean to ask a question.
J1, that's literally all he says.
Let me ask a question.
It's like, dude, stop asking fucking questions all the time,
dawg.
By the way, why are they talking about me for I didn't do anything. No, there's always everywhere. I go they're mentioning you
They're mentioning you and then uh, they're gonna put a little respect on it
But I can't rewind it because it's like it's like they he makes it so you can't rewind live
Which is lame. I think I don't like how they do that like where it's like, you know
You have to be watching it live
You can't go back but what if you miss have to show and then you you don't know what they're talking about it's like
And they're talking about Chris Hall and stuff like that
Chris Hall is a nice man, isn't he?
Tell them to put a little respect on my name.
Yeah, I will.
Hey, put respect on Ghost's name.
I don't know what they're talking about.
Don't ever compare me to J-Bone.
That's disrespectful.
Yeah.
I don't know what they're talking about.
Dropping the ice cream.
I don't know what they're talking about there.
Did you drop any ice cream, Ghost?
Nah, not that I remember no, I don't think so he's like dollar gate you owe me an apology run for scamming at a $50
I think at this point Sam Sammy Sammy my boys Sammy owes me an apology at this point
Sam and you have to apologize to ghosts. Yeah, you hear this ghost wants an apology
Yep, clip it and ship it boys. Yep. We're gonna clip it and ship it
Yeah, Sam and like is playing all his stuff on rumble now though. He like puts his episodes on rumble himself and
You know, I don't know it's like I mean it's so funny like people watching because he like is about the drama and stuff
But it's like it's kind of like boring. He plays over an hour of music to start the show and it's like I can't
It's like I just don't understand like I mean I play like I play like a little song and like people get all mad
I mean it's an hour of music and people just sit there for hours and like it's crazy. I guess they
Know I don't know what they're talking about. He's like he wishes. Let's see
Okay, yeah
So I'm here with Lenore. Lenore's in my lap. She's so soft. So what do you what do you have to hurry?
What are you doing anything today?
Well, I think I just got triggered for the second time because there's like three
I can only get triggered three times a day. Yeah, you got very triggered. What what what what triggered you?
The first one was you know talking about cats got triggered by that the second one is Sammy's letting people talk shit on his channel about me
And then the third one if I have something to do with you
Yeah, mostly
I
Figure you're talking about Sam and let me see
They probably know that we're watching
Watching off stream here
Link up
Sammy does he want me to join if he asked nicely and apologizes I would join
I didn't applaud you for it, Jesus.
The essence in the bottle, you're filming me.
Oh, my god.
I'm not eating that water.
It's splendid.
Ew.
I got some.
Tronky toast.
Mine went to, like, beating and, like, uh, mouthwrapping shit.
No, no, no.
Sink the reeling in bigger fish with the stench.
No.
hell back in the day amber streams was in the bathroom 100%
they were i think you saw Amber was coming over and nappy ass here she's
at the headset and all i don't remember that's not the amber
don't you ever
i looked at her coming through those f*****g nap nigga that's the series
Amber was sweating in there the amber got to eat with the headset
Go ahead, 2-2-5.
Ain't nobody can knock you.
Ain't nobody knock you anywhere in the book.
I'm going.
All right.
Well, you're on this gentleman.
The fucking door that she was talking about was an antique door.
Oh, my antique door.
I can't get a pain to this antique.
What?
That door about to break down.
I don't remember that door.
Like the type of bitch that is seller on D's on eBay though
She don't wear underwear bridge
Bag with Michael with the police. She wasn't wearing no
Come on, Bridget imagine this Bridget Bridget imagine this you you you have a fiance
Your fiancee decides to go out with four other men with no bro. No panties and a dress on imagine that
Imagine that
Panties and a dress on with four niggas
Crazy to the end crazy
Cool
Let's see I can play you one more thing before I go. I mean we're gonna get it real quick
So Q this is Q last year on
Somebody's show and or it's not another show actually and he's like saying like, you know
You know like that basically that I'm gonna get my channel taken down and he owns the song
What's the welcome to the night? You know the DJ like your song. He says he owns it and stuff
But it's like I'll show you what it looks like if you want to see before we go Google Drive
in second
Because it was really retarded and so is Tony. I mean Tony's retarded too. It's like so system dumb
But yeah, he was like trying to like say oh my god, Tony's so smart
He figured I had to take out psyche and so it's just like lame as fuck, but let's see if I have it still let me see if I have it
Is it here?
No.
OK.
Is it here?
I'm thinking of doing another one.
Let me switch to this here.
Yeah, I have it.
OK, so we're ready to see.
I mean, if I can download this real quick and share it.
OK, download.
Yeah, I got it.
So, this is Q last year, after when I was getting copyright struck by that douchebag,
and he's working with them and stuff like that, so you can hear him brag about it.
He thinks my channel is going to go down, and he's like, oh my gosh, I wish I knew how
to do this, because I wouldn't do this to Zaya and Pebs, and everybody always gets everyone
off the internet.
So, here we go.
This is it.
Oops, let me just go to the...
Where's my streamer?
I'm lost, hold on a second.
Around here. So here it is. Okay. Okay, so I'll take this down and here it is. What's this? Oh, yeah shit
Okay, I'll take that off. Okay. So here it is. This is Q45 bragging about some bullshit
anyways, um, so
we have a new channel intro that
Somebody made for me and I want to give a really big special shout out to my friend
Some of you know him as different things.
He goes by a few different things on YouTube.
But I think maybe you might all know him best
as Tony or Allied Master Computer.
So thank you for the new intro.
I appreciate it, man.
Here it goes.
Get out the show.
Star shine is so bright.
Watch the secrets unfold.
But thank you guys the new channel intro. I don't know what the video is about
I have no clue what the fuck is on the video, but I thought it looked cool and shout out to Tony for making that for me
This is original artwork by the way
That people tried to steal
He thinks he's so funny so dorky dork dance to the mystery
I can't, that's all I have.
I cut the video down because you don't need
fucking two minutes of the rest of the song.
The first 50 seconds are enough.
The intro was too fucking long, I made it better, okay?
You don't need two minute intro,
especially when you're restarting the stream
every fucking five minutes.
So most of that motherfucker's streams were shorter
than the intro, like the actual stream itself
is shorter than the fucking intro.
You think I can stick psyche up for 50 bucks for the intro? Nope
Not a penny hands up don't shoot
Jeepers you want to get kicked out of the chat?
You lost Tony if you're in here. Yeah, tell fucking psyche to catch
Okay
Just to say psyche W. Oh, that's too good. Let me just say this too
You niggas out there are lucky that I don't know how to do what Tony did because none of you would have channels
There wouldn't be no fucking Zeya. There wouldn't be no Peds. There wouldn't be no fucking Samans
None of you niggas
If I had the power to do a Tony did the psyche there wouldn't be a community anymore. I wouldn't wipe all of you out
He admitted he was just y'all are lucky. I don't know how to do what he did so lucky
I would wipe the whole fucking shit out. There's whole fucking place gone zapped in a day
I do it all in one day to it be like it would be like you is up either against my father part, too
You know when he go when everybody gets fucking whacked or is that in the first one?
It's at the end of the first one or it's the middle of the second one whenever he just goes and fucking whacks everybody
Yeah, Tony the conductor
If I knew how to do what Tony did, nobody around here would have channels like I would be I'm way too fucking reckless to have that type of knowledge.
Oh, I fuck everybody shit up everybody.
Well, not everybody, but the people that I really don't fucking like.
Yeah, I would, I would make sure that every time you fucking went live, I copyright struck it every time Benjamin Kowalski, you would know that fucking name.
Oh, he talks, he knocks them, he knocks them.
You better hope to fucking God. I never get that knowledge
second
Second what?
That wall, you know what? I'm not sure exactly if it is the same truth finder method
And I know what that method is
I don't want I'm not gonna say it cuz I don't want to give too many of these people like all it is people too many different ideas
I do somebody and I know well take out your channel what the
The process is technique like loosely, but I don't know how to actually make it work
like it, you know, because I'm not gonna go through all that bullshit and then fucking
it not even work, you know, like go through filling out all that bullshit and then by the
time you get to the end of filling all of it out and do a quick thing that doesn't even work,
you know, um, I don't I don't know. Yeah, I know I heard you're not worth it. There's a theory.
I don't think anybody knows a hundred percent
See that's I don't know. I thought that the truth finder thing was
Was kind of like up in the air like people guessed what he did
But nobody really knew exactly how he did that like how he fucking just went and struck everybody shit
Like he got player one and all them like I don't know if anybody knows exactly how he did it
I think a lot of people have theories with different based on like uploading it to different websites and then coming back to YouTube and saying
Gotcha
You know, cause YouTube isn't gonna ask no questions.
And that's what these fucking idiots over there,
these stupid fucking retarded, middle-aged,
menopause-made-in fucking tarot hoes,
sitting over there telling him like,
Hey, thank you.
I just looked it up online,
and the copyright, you know what I'm saying?
And they're going to say, well, this guy can't prove that he owns the copyright.
So we're automatically going to give it to the one who's making the claim in the first place.
But no, we have a bunch of these fucking 40 to fucking 55, 60 year old women on here that
think that they know how this shit works.
You don't know shit, bitch.
You've had, you have fucking 300, 400 sub channels
and think all of a sudden you know about how YouTube works
and you're trying to tell a nigga like me
how this shit works.
I've been monetized on the same channel for three years.
I need more.
No strikes, no private or no copyright strikes,
no fucking community guidelines strikes.
I mean, I've had them before, but they're gone now.
You know, they go away.
Nothing, channel completely clean.
Don't sit here and try to tell me
how the fuck YouTube works, bitch.
Gonna try to tell me well, I looked it up on Google and copyright law says that you can't copyright it AI song
All right
Well, why don't you fucking call YouTube and prove to them that it's an AI song because you can't
Nobody can you can just because you say it's an AI song doesn't like YouTube doesn't fucking know that YouTube doesn't care to know
That they don't give a fuck. They're gonna look at it. They're gonna be like, okay
We're awarding it to the claimer because the defendant in the situation can't prove that it's theirs either wrong
And then, oh, guess what happens?
Psyche wakes up and he looks on his computer.
And what does Psyche see?
That all of the fucking the claims
that he made got denied.
Nope.
Oh!
They all got accepted.
You mean to tell me that Christine in summer
and fucking DJ Electra aren't experts on copyright law,
especially when it comes to YouTube?
Who would have fucking guessed?
Who would have ever guessed?
I don't know if they were.
Can't believe it, right?
Amazing.
So, you know me as soon as that happened. I had to go back into that fucking bitch Christine's chat and be like
Told you bitch
Fucking old menopause bitches on here acting like they know something you don't know shit. You don't know shit. Nope. He does some
Okay, so is that it? Let me see. Yeah, I think that was it. Okay. Let me look hold on a second
I have another one to show you too. This is Tony actually on Samans channel last year. It's pretty funny. Watch this
Yeah, this was last year or this funny
Playing bro, I'm going to fucking all out war Sam and stripes dude. We're playing dirty, bro
We're gonna play super fucking dirty
Tony world order, bro
It's mine, bro, so you want me can I sort of screenshot?
Absolutely this is what I fucking got sent to me in a walker. I got a fucking took me out of my beauty sleep, man
And that really pissed me off
Sike hands up don't shoot sake Tony said this rules you gotta ask between you and Tony
These rules we have to follow bro, and he's not follow them
Someone's got to hold them accountable. I am that man
That this is what this is a wall suit that I got fucking said to me, right?
There's strikes because you can't figure out how to fucking take the strikes down
I am being threatened with the fucking lawsuit and I think it's a very fucking funny because he's got he's run out of options
He's got nothing
You know, I am the rightful owner of that song, and he doesn't realize that, and he's trying every step of the way that he can to fucking take my song away from me, and I'm not going to let that happen.
Do you understand that, Sam?
I just own the song.
You know, but did you actually spend the $5 or the $10 or whatever it is to register the song.
Go ahead.
Don't know
Yeah, he's bullshit
That's tragic nigga. How you talk I told my you claim shit, you know, you know, you want to spend the money to fucking
Run it through a fucking
Obviously, I own it because fucking psyche can't go live on that channel dummy
I'm asking you, did you register the song?
Who did you run the song through?
CD Baby, who?
Who you ran the song through?
Dude, that's for me to fucking know,
and for you to fucking find out.
Yeah, he bullshit, I'm bullshit.
All I'm saying is you better hope he didn't run it through,
and he actually has proof,
because if you use your channel,
you know you can lose your channel, right?
I don't give a fuck about channels, dude.
I will lose 6,000 channel to fuck with this guy, dude.
He'll fucking care.
Ew.
How you didn't really run the program?
I'm not answering your fucking pathetic ass questions.
Why you didn't run it?
Why you didn't run it through the program?
Actually, it's so cheap to register a track.
Negative.
It's so cheap.
It's real machinations.
Machinations.
Because you can't register.
That's crazy.
And no one can use that song but psyche and electro.
Your country can't use the song, but everyone else can.
That's who I get permission to.
Can I ask you a question?
Good thank you. Who's this? Thank you. Who is this? It's not her. It's not her who's this in my profile picture
I'm random woman. No. Whoa. Whoa. No borrow. No
All right, you'll change your profile picture though. Come on. I'm not changing my profile picture
That's like he's warrior apparently that's his response to the copyright claim
Y'all gotta hope that that person didn't work through.
Yeah, RJ, that is DJ Electro.
That's Electro, not her.
My profile picture is DJ Electro.
And got a copy written for the five or $10.
You're fucked.
Psyche's gonna get the music back
and then you're gonna get in trouble for force flagging.
That's crazy.
Who cares?
I will lose a thousand fucking channels
to try this thing.
Dude, I don't care.
The original creator of this track,
Published. Damn.
Did they talk to my publisher?
Damn.
Why don't you take me to court, dude? I'm not afraid of them.
Let them take me to court, dude.
I've got fucking deer pockets.
That looks official right there. I ain't gonna hold you.
That looks super official.
Yeah, she's in the industry, bro.
Let her take me to court, bro. I'm not afraid.
Oh, we got the single part. This is real.
That's fine.
This is not that I'm talking about the eat the the copyright shit and whatever
Yeah, this is real, but Tony's saying it's real. Oh
No, I'm not saying that's true. I'm saying I'm calling his bluff
I'm calling the psyches bluff. This is all bullshit. No, it's like you come on
Take the money to take me to court. I want you to
Hey talking about publishing in that shit
Cease and desist. God damn.
Take me to court over a lawsuit, please.
No, I'm talking about you know the person on YouTube gets this right and they read this
They're gonna be so petrified because this is legal jargon. They use and they use in legal jargon, right?
Look violation section 512 f of the DMCA right so they use in statutes, right?
Yo, yeah, this is this is no I'm not saying that this is they think this is real
But I'm saying it's a bluff, I think this is all bullshit.
It's a bluff that shit is already sent.
That's fine, let him send it.
How you calling it a bluff and it's already sent?
But what you don't understand is, you don't understand.
I'm going to keep striking.
Do you know what the term bluff means?
Yeah, you can take me to court. Let him take me to court. No, what I'm saying is you say he's bluffing with that shit
But it's not it's not it's pending too. It's not even notarized. This is all this ain't this ain't fucking notarized
This is bullshit. It's not notarized
email
Can I say notarized? How do you get a nice email? How do you get that? You can't so it's bullshit
But what's I could do to just to end it he don't want the war
Like the claim the strike that Tony gave this this is a counter strike. This is like a counter
All they did was respond to the copyright claim that
That Tony put on psyche right and now look at what they doing on psyche that
No, it's not a counter. They emailed YouTube and CC'd me.
Whoever wrote this is on point.
But regardless, I'm taking the strikes now.
Let me get a dick.
I don't want to put this faggot.
I don't I don't want to fucking I don't want to the fucking channel.
They got a hyperlink to everything there, bro.
I'm running them out.
So there we go.
That was that shit.
Know it's like but it was all troll the queue and him were just trolling because they're just losers and I was new
And I didn't really I was kind of maybe like worried about for 10 minutes
But like really it's nothing to worry about. I was just monetized. I think when that happened maybe and so
Probably just jealous and you know
Whatever
Okay, I guess I'll play on the way out. I'll play the
the Alexandra, yeah, it was hate speech.
I mean, I've said that before on my show, though,
so I don't get offended, but it is kind of like,
some people could get offended,
some people committed suicide over that kind of shit,
so you have to be careful.
But you say sometimes, let me see, like, you know,
let me see one second.
This is, I made this with Alexandra's inspiration,
Oh, yeah, here it is, and then I'll see you guys later. I'll be back tonight here in a second. Here you go
Um, where am I here? Yeah, I love you guys
Watch me ascent
The light is the canvas where visions move
My voice cries
Close up through cosmic darkness
And my walls in one circle, dear